Wayne: [Sniffs] What-what’s that smell?
How do we find that smell?
Baaulp: What smell? What
smell are you talking about?
Wayne: I don’t know, where do we begin?
[A moment of silence passes]
Wayne: [Laughs weakly] The truth of the
matter is that in order to find a smell,
you would sniff until you locate it. Welcome to
another episode of the Where Do We Begin podcast,
uh, this episode, nominated for
“Worst Intro of the Year,” uh—
Baaulp, laughing: Smell—“What’s that
smell?” That’s all we got, oh my god.
Trog: We could rerecord it.
Wayne: Hey, I liked it. I’m Wayne.
Trog: I’m Trog.
Log: Log.
Baaulp: I’m Baaulp.
Gir: And I’m Gir.
Wayne: And that’s everyone. And we are here
tonight with discussions. All kinds of things.
Gir: Oh boy, oh boy, I love discussions.
Wayne: The date is October
seventh, 2020, and we are in the
month of the pumpkin. The time of the ghost.
Gir: That’s right, this is—this is—
Wayne: It’s Halloween month, baby.
Gir: The month of Halloween.
Wayne: This is our Halloween episode and we’ve
got scary smells, deadspace3.com/smell, uh—
Gir: I find it interesting that as a holiday that
you celebrate for five hours out of the night,
one day out of the year, is celebrated
pretty much the entire month of October.
Wayne: So is Christmas!
Baaulp: Yeah, they want money, people want money.
Gir: Christmas can be an all-day
thing, though. You can eat
a meal all day, you can open presents all day—
Wayne: If you’re a really diehard pumpkin fan—
Trog: You can’t celebrate Halloween all day.
Gir: [Crosstalk] Halloween—No, Halloween—
Wayne: Alright, alright, alright.
So I’m gonna describe you
how to celebrate Halloween all day.
You wake up, you wake your kids up, you
scare them. You give them a little
chainsaw scare to wake them up outta bed.
[Baaulp and Trog laugh]
Wayne: Then you feed them a pumpkin—like a
pumpkin flavored breakfast, maybe pumpkin
pancakes, I bet those would be delicious.
Baaulp: What? Okay, that sounds good though, yeah.
Wayne: And then you get them-you
get them in costume, because
they’re gonna go to school in costume
because there’s a costume party at school—
Gir: Unless it’s Saturday.
Wayne: And then they come home and
then they go trick-or-treating.
Listen, so, every five out of seven years
you can celebrate Halloween all day.
And even then you can probably make some
tweaks for-for the morning. If you don’t
have kids, then no, you can’t, but
if you have kids you can do it.
Gir: No, the spirit of Halloween is once the sun
is down,
sorry.
Wayne: I mean that’s-that’s at its peak—
Trog: Yeah, you-you just
can’t be scary in the light.
Gir: ‘Cause then the rest of
that’s no different than the
rest of the fucking month.
Baaulp: Halloween to me has never
been a holiday about sc—about
being actually scared. It’s just a holiday
about eating candy and dressing up.
Wayne: That’s one element! Fuckin’ scary stuff
is a core element to Halloween, are you crazy?
Log: It’s a theme that’s easy
to get into. The theme of the
month is horror, scary stuff!
Wayne: It is not common practice
to celebrate Halloween for
the entirety of the day like you would
Christmas, but you could. You absolutely
could if you were a diehard Halloween
fan and I guarantee you there are people
who do.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: So, email in wheredowebeginqa,
do you celebrate Halloween
all day?
Baaulp: I know for a fact that
people do that because people
will like—people around here, they’ll
go to Salem, Massachusetts, they’ll just
go and they’ll just like, party. And it’s like,
they-they like—it like—that’s—it’s—Salem’s
a pretty normal place but like, during
Halloween they turn into a tourist town,
where like you go and it’s like, “Oh,
let’s check out where they burn witches,
and then go drinking and eat candy, I guess.”
Gir: Do you think there’s
somebody who wakes up Halloween
morning and the first thing out of
their mouth is just like, “Oh, boo!
Halloween!” They just realize what
day it is, “Oh, boo! Scary day!”
Wayne: I spent a lot of time
on the Internet, and people
love this fuckin’ holiday, man.
Log: It’s the only time that has
like a cool theme to it, it’s
like, supernatural stuff,
it’s weird stuff, y’know.
Wayne: [Crosstalk] It’s, yeah,
[Wayne sings part of the Goosebumps
theme song].
Log: Like, it’s so broad like,
you got creatures and also
like, magical beings. The occult.
Things like that, it’s-it’s cool stuff,
it’s fantastical stuff. If come November you
come in here and you’re all like, pilgrimcore,
you got your buckle hat, you’ll get
shoved into a locker ‘cause what
good is
that?
Wayne: Now thanks—Thanksgiving, that’s a
holiday you do not celebrate all month.
Log: Yeah, you don’t do any uh,
Captain-Captain John
Arbuckle cosplay.
Gir: Thanksgiving’s a day where
you completely gorge yourself
on that day, anyway. You’re going to overindulge
on one day, you don’t need to
spread it through the month.
Wayne: Can we all agree,
all members of this podcast,
Thanksgiving is one of the worst holidays?
Baaulp: Uhh—
Gir: No.
Trog: Umm, I don’t know.
Wayne: I think it sucks shit.
Gir: Saint Patrick’s Day is stupid.
Trog: I’m pretty neutral.
Wayne: Out of the major holidays, I think
Thanksgiving sucks shit. I mean sure,
you can eat some food, but
like, you can do that any day.
Gir: Well then what are the major holidays?
Trog: Are we counting Easter as a major holiday?
Gir: Yeah, ‘cause I would say Easter
sucks more shit than Thanksgiving.
Wayne: I don’t know…
Gir: [Laughs] When’s the last
time you celebrated Easter?
When you were seven?
Wayne: Hey, I eat eggs on Easter.
Trog: I think you can chart, like—
Wayne: And I like eggs more than turkey.
Trog: It’s like a line graph,
right? It’s like a line graph
where the x-axis is your age, and the
y-axis is your enjoyment of a holiday.
And I feel like Easter starts high, and
then just asymptotically approaches no
enjoyment at all until you just
stop celebrating it entirely.
Baaulp: I’m not Christian, I
have never celebrated Easter in
earnest, that’s honestly, again, it’s
just a day where you have fun and eat a
lot of candy.
Wayne: Now, I don’t always do
this, but Easter—Even if I don’t
celebrate Easter, Easter do be
having that post-holiday candy sales.
Trog: Sure.
Gir: Well, so does like, every other candy-based—
Wayne: Not Thanksgiving! You can’t
get discount candy on Thanksgiving!
Trog: That’s true, there’s
no Thanksgiving candy, and if
there was it’d be gross.
Gir: You can get discount turkeys!
Trog: Like, turkey lollipop.
Wayne: Who the fuck—I do not buy
discount turkey on Thanksgiving,
something about that sounds heinous.
Gir: You get a discount turkey on Black Friday.
Wayne: You want this old meat that didn’t make it?
Gir: No, that’s the thing,
though, is you get Thanksgiving
done and it’s like, “Alright! [Claps
once] Tomorrow we’re gonna buy everything
dirt fucking cheap,” ‘cause
the next day is Black Friday.
Log: Buy our dying corn.
Wayne: Yeah, but Black Friday sucks so much shit.
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] Yeah, Black Friday sucks.
Wayne: It by-by principle, brings Thanksgiving’s
volumes
down.
Gir: Oh, I can buy electronics for half price, so…
Wayne: I think-I think also
what the holiday of Thanksgiving
stands for is also bad.
Gir: What it stands for is thank-being thankful,
that doesn’t mean that’s what
actually happened [laughs].
Wayne: Yeah, that’s the base
level symbolism of the holiday.
Log: I think if you, if you
trace it back to like, any
historical moment it’ll probably be bad.
Wayne, laughing: Yeah.
Log: We don’t really know what
they were getting up to at
All Hallows’ Eve or whatever the fuck.
Baaulp: April Fool’s day was so fucked up.
Log: Yeah, the original? The first fool?
Like, they’ve toned
fools down since then.
Wayne: The first trick killed
like, ten people, absolutely.
[Baaulp laughs]
Log: Like, a jester’s domesticated,
you don’t know what a
fool is like.
[Baaulp, Wayne, and Gir laugh]
Gir: A domesticated fool is a jester.
Wayne: I mean it’s a sh—they
had jesters domesticated but
like, they got wiped out. You don’t see
jesters anymore, they went extinct. So,
domestication couldn’t save them.
Gir: It’s true.
Log: I wanna say though, from
like a pragmatic point of
view, Easter is preferable to Thanksgiving
because it’s always on a Sunday, right?
Trog: Mhmm.
Log: Because, so if like a
standard 9 to 5, five-days-a-week
work week, they’ll always give you the Friday
off instead of the Sunday ‘cause y’know,
that doesn’t count.
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] Oh, yeah,
you’re right. You’re right.
Trog: But if that’s the argument,
then Thanksgiving is always
on a Thursday, yeah.
Log: Thanksgiving’s on a Thursday, they don’t give
you the Friday
off.
Trog: Really? I’ve—
Baaulp: What?
Log: You-You—You go to work,
you have a Thanksgiving Day
off, and then you have to go
back to work for that Friday.
Wayne: Yeah, I’ve never worked
a job where they gave me the
Friday off. I haven’t had a
Thanksgiving Friday off since school.
Log: It’s a waste.
Wayne: They haven’t done that
since I was in fuckin’ high
school. Every job I’ve worked,
Thursday, you do not get Friday.
Trog: I guess it depends.
Log: You got Thanksgiving
Thursday, wasteful Friday—
Wayne: Dark Friday.
Trog: It depends on if you’re
working in a retail position
or not, ‘cause I haven’t worked
retail so like, I would always get—
Gir: Retail you don’t get
anything off, are you kidding?
Trog: I would always get Thursday-Friday off.
Log: I don’t work retail
and I don’t get Friday off.
Baaulp: You’re getting screwed
there, ‘cause I’ve—Ever since—Every
non-retail job I’ve had yeah, you get
the Friday after Thanksgiving off.
Trog: It’s just a long weekend.
Wayne: Well, I’ve only ever
worked jobs that were retail or
retail-adjacent, so.
Gir: I’ve only had one job
besides streaming, literally only
the—Well, I’ve had multiple positions in
the same company, but it was always—I’ve
only worked for one company in my life.
Wayne: Yeah, meatman, fruitman,
moneyman, you did it all.
Gir: Yeah—
Wayne: Master of grocers.
Gir: I liked the-I liked the-I
liked the produce thing, I didn’t
like the retail bit.
Wayne: Yeah, moneyman is the
worst role to play. Nobody
likes to be the moneyman.
Gir: I didn’t like how I
had to work every holiday.
Wayne: Yeah, that sucks shit.
Gir: Like, mandatory.
Wayne: That sucks a fatty.
Gir: I will say though, I
got lucky, I only had to work
Christmas one year, but holy shit, what
a fuckin’ miserable experience working
Christmas day.
Wayne: Working at the pet store,
uh, my days off were always
Thursday and Friday, that had two
downsides. One, anytime a holiday
would fall on a Thursday, I wouldn’t
get an extra day off, which was always
upsetting, uh, like a—Basically,
Thanksgiving always sucked because it was
like, “Okay, here’s a day that
you would normally have like,
to do whatever the
fuck you want,”—
Gir: Mhmm.
Wayne: “But no, like, everyone else is getting
off work and you have to be fully occupied going
out somewhere or whatever. You have to celebrate
Thanksgiving. And then the other downs—But-but
the pros, the upside to that was I never worked
a single Black Friday because I always had Friday
off. They never-they never got me. They tried,
I think there was one year—I think there was
one year where they tried to pull me in, and I was
like, “Nah, it’s my day off and I’m gonna be outta
town for Thanksgiving,” which was a lie, I never
fucking leave town for Thanksgiving [laughs].
Gir: I lied—I lied through
my fuckin’ teeth at work.
Baaulp: You were just hiding in a cave instead.
Wayne: [Laughs] Yeah, I had to hide in a cave or
else they’d
find me.
Gir: That completely reminded me, uh, I
remember when I got so fed up with like,
after that Christmas that I worked, I got
so fed up with that shit that come January,
I was like, “Okay, this year I’m
setting a fucking—I’m setting two
days that I will not work,” because you
can set that as a schedule restriction,
and uh, I was like, “Alright, let me look
at the calendar for the end of this year,
when does Christmas happen this year, and like,
Oh, Christmas Eve is like Tuesday, Christmas day
is like, Wednesday. Alright, I’m never working
Tuesdays or Wednesdays, don’t even call me on
Tuesdays or Wednesdays.” And that worked out
so fucking well [laughs] ‘cause it guaranteed
one year I wouldn’t have to work Christmas day,
the next year I wouldn’t have to work Christmas
day. And then this year I would’ve had to but
then I said, “Fuck you,” and left [laughs].
Baaulp: Nice. Calculated.
Gir: Calculated.
Trog: We kind of gone off from
the Halloween discussion, but
I’d like to reign us back in towards the
spooky month of the year, is that okay
with everybody? Are you too
scared to continue discussing it?
Gir: No.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: ‘Cause I was thinking uh,
I was thinking earlier today
actually, about like, do you guys remember
what you dressed up as for Halloween
as a kid?
Wayne: Yes, I do! I remember every single one.
Baaulp: I’m gonna be so real,
I have never dressed up for
Halloween, every.
Wayne: What?
Trog: How did you get candy?
Wayne: Wow.
Baaulp: I didn’t. I didn’t go trick-or-treating.
Trog: Oh.
Baaulp: I never went trick-or-treating.
So, it’s a combination of me asking for
a costume to go trick-or-treating
and my parents saying, “You’re not
going to go to people’s—stranger’s houses to
get candy, and we can’t afford a costume, so…”
Trog: Okay, well Baaulp, Baaulp,
what I want you to do Baaulp,
is I want you to come up with what you would have—
Baaulp: Power Ranger.
[Gir laughs]
Trog: —gone as as a kid,
while everybody else I want—
[Wayne sings a bit of the Mighty
Morphin Power Rangers theme]
Trog: I want to hear from
everybody else what your favorite
childhood Halloween costume was. I’m interested.
Wayne: Uh, favorite how so?
Favorite looking back as an
adult and laughing at it, favorite? Or
favorite like that was the one I enjoyed
the most as a kid?
Trog: Hmm, I mean feel free to give both.
Wayne: Both? I somehow remember
every single costume. Like,
I—For whatever reason, I—Halloween at
the trick-or-treating age was much more
special than any other holiday, I
think. And the memories stand stronger
because you had like—There’s so much
variation in Halloween. Both with like what
costume you wear and what you did. Like,
the people that you go trick-or-treating
with, like whoever you’re hanging out
with and where you go and what you
actually partake in on that Halloween
night. Like Christmas never fucking
changes other than like, what you get.
Thanksgiving never changes other than
like, did you eat marshmallow
casserole or black bean casserole?
Gir: Ew!
Wayne: Um, that’s not a dish.
Black bean casserole isn’t
real. Unless it is and you can fucking
email me your anger, you have that way
to do that. Uh, so favorite Halloween
costume when I was a kid that I enjoyed
the most? Did you-did any of you guys
ever see or dress up as a wraith?
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: Like, like a black—It was
like a black robe with a hood
that had—It was like a cloak with a hood
that had like a mesh mask over it so
that you could see through
it but no one could see in?
Trog: Yeah.
Gir: Yeah.
Gir: That’s literally the only one I had-I could
remember, is
that one.
Trog: Yep.
Wayne: And like, so you couldn’t
see into it but it had these
like, weird glasses you could wear
that had like, glowing red eyes.
Gir: Oh, I didn’t have glowing eyes.
Wayne: Yeah, it was dope!
The-the actual like apparatus was
strange. But my favorite as an adult,
because it was fucking funny, I think
from the ages of like, three to six, I
think three years in a row or something
like that, I went as Bibleman?
[Gir laughs]
Trog: Hell yeah.
Wayne: I’ve told you guys about
this, Bibleman is a straight-to-VHS
action hero uh, he is a yellow and
purple cop man with like a yellow light
saber that he doesn’t use because he
wins by convincing the villains to read
the Bible or some shit, he like never
uses the light saber, and when I was a
kid I thought he was so fuckin’ cool. And
now and days I think that’s probably just
because of the color scheme, I was a
child that was attracted to bright colors—
[Trog and Baaulp laugh]
Wayne: —and I was brainwashed into Christianity,
so like bright colors and brainwashing, y’know,
I had to love Bibleman, you had to. And then like,
when I was a little kid it was Buzz Lightyear
and Bibleman, those were my two favorite things.
Gir: Hell yeah, Buzz Lightyear.
Wayne: [Unintelligible] Buzz Lightyear a bunch and
Bibleman those
were my-those were my favorite.
Gir: Literally all-the only
one I can remember—For some
reason I don’t remember like any of my
costumes except for like that wraith one
that you were describing, uh, I didn’t
have light up eyes, but I do remember it
being one of the more comfortable costumes
I’d ever worn and it was still incredibly
uncomfortable [laughs]. I don’t think
I once went trick-or-treating in a
costume that didn’t make me feel
uncomfortable after like fifteen minutes.
Wayne: Yeah, I have a lot of
discomfort Halloween memories,
like I dressed up as a werewolf one year
and the costume was so fucking hot I
was gonna die, and I was like, that
combined with all the walking around, I was
an out of shape child, it was horrible.
Trog: My picks are um,
whenever I—I legitimately don’t
remember how old I was, I had to have been
elementary school age for both of these,
but one was I went as Sonic the Hedgehog
and my mom made the costume for me—
Wayne: Sick.
Trog: She like-she like made
these like, felt spine things
to put on a hood, that was cool.
Um, the weird one, and the one that made me
think of this question in the first place,
is I had like a brain memory return
to me of like, being a kid and deciding that
I wanted to—This is super fucking
obscure, I wanted to, as a kid,
for Halloween, be Quailman. Do any of you know
what that is off the top of your head?
Wayne: Yeah, I know Quailman! From fucking Doug!
Baaulp: From Doug?
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: What?
Wayne: We had a high school
teacher that every Halloween
would dress a Quailman and he would
rollerblade into every classroom.
Gir: I don’t know what that is.
Trog: Okay, so there was a TV
show called Doug, let’s see-let’s
start there. Well, actually, let’s start—
Gir: I hated Doug.
Trog: So, there’s a TV network called Nickelodeon—
Wayne: Let’s tell him about Doug.
So, Doug is this little bald
bitch—
Gir: I hated Doug.
Baaulp: So, Viacom is a—
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: So, television—
Log: So, Doug can go faster—
Wayne: What was wrong with Doug? Hold on—
Trog: So, a cathode-ray tube
television is a big vacuum—
Gir: Doug sucked!
Baaulp: An electron is a particle that—
Trog: So, quantum foam—
Wayne: Gir, why’d you—Gir,
tell me why you hated Doug.
Gir: You wanted me-you want me
to tell you why I hated Doug?
He wasn’t funny.
Wayne: What?
Trog: He was literally funny.
Wayne: But he broke grill, he sorry.
Gir: That video’s funny.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: I just remembered I wanted
to be Quailman and thinking
about that now it’s like—Oh, by the way,
if you don’t know what the fuck we’re
talking about, there’s literally a TV
show called Doug that was on Nickelodeon—
Wayne: About a little bald kid.
Trog: —and Doug had an alter-ego
superhero called Quailman
which was just him wearing
a-like a green, sleeveless vest—
Wayne: Which he always wore.
Trog: —with like a cape with a
Q on it, and there was a belt,
there was a belt wrapped around his
forehead and wore underpants on top of his
regular pants. So that was Quailman,
so imagine like a five year-old
dressed up
like that.
Gir: [Laughs] I would laugh my ass off.
Log: It’s so weird to me that
you liked Doug at that age.
That was like, the type of
cartoon that I filed into,
“Only good whenever you’re
an adult.”
Trog: I-I liked Doug, Doug was good.
Log: That’s how I categorize it,
like that was-that was the cartoon
that I watched whenever I had chickenpox
and I was just in bed for a week.
Trog: [Laughs] Well you’re a
little younger than me, so I
don’t know, maybe you missed the Doug boat.
Baaulp: I’m inclined to agree with Log,
and I disagree with Gir, because like,
as a—you’re right, Log, as a child
I don’t think I—I knew of Doug and I
watched a few episodes and I didn’t think it
was that funny, now as an adult I think the
concept of someone having a crush on a girl
named Patti Mayonnaise is incredibly funny.
Wayne: Gir, I shat on you for
saying Doug sucked but I also
didn’t like Doug when I was
a kid, so I don’t even know
what I was talking
about [laughs].
Gir: Yeah. I remember specifically—
Wayne: Doug had a vibe that
was specifically anti-child.
Gir: Yeah. Yeah.
Wayne: I think it like, repels children.
Baaulp: No, it was anti-Doug.
Trog: It was [unintelligible].
Gir, laughing hard: Doug—it was anti-Doug? What?
[Wayne laughs]
Log: Doug was in high school, wasn’t he?
Trog: Nuh-uh.
Log: That was like a cartoon that took pl—was
it middle
school?
Trog: It was middle school.
Wayne: I think if you were a
middle schooler when it aired
you probably could appreciate it more,
I was like. Young. When it aired.
Gir: I was like ten.
Trog: Yeah, I mean, like, like
I said, I mean me, Gir, and
Baaulp are the same age but Wayne and
Log are both younger than the three of
us, so I think maybe you guys—
Gir: Mhmm.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: Because to be fair,
Doug got really bad, it was a
Nickelodeon show—I almost said it was a
Nintendo show, my brain is not working—
[Gir laughs]
Trog: Um, it was a Nickelodeon
show but then they sold it
off to Disney, and uh, they made it bad.
Baaulp: Yeah, Disney just fucking
ruined it. ‘Cause it was a
very like Hey Arnold!-esque show where
it’s like, Doug was an underdog, he’s
not cool, he’s specifically not cool, right?
Wayne: But he can go faster.
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: He can Doug or he can faster.
Baaulp: It’s through that that
it’s endearing, and I-I just
like the names as an adult ‘cause
Doug has a friend named Skeeter—
Gir: [Crosstalk] Skeeter.
Trog and Gir: Yeah.
Baaulp: And he’s-and he has
a crush on a girl whose last
name is Mayonnaise.
Trog: Yeah, it’s kind of a
weird—like thinking about it, it
kind of makes sense that I
like it, thinking about what
I like now, ‘cause it’s
kind of a bizarre show—
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: —where it’s just a cartoon
and like a good amount of
the time of an episode is always
dedicated to Doug having these anxiety
daydreams.
Baaulp: A panic attack.
Trog: Yeah, like these panic
attack, anxiety daydreams where
he just thinks of the worst possible outcome
to his current situation. Like that-that
was like the thing, like Doug is just
this like little nerdy like, anxious kid
and it’s like, “Wow, I can relate to this.”
Gir: [Crosstalk] Bitch.
Baaulp: Yeah, it’s a very
endearing-it’s a very endearing
show, that’s why I sort of have a soft spot
for it from the few episodes I watched,
I got it.
Wayne: Hey, what the fuck was
up with that blue kid that
honked at him.
Trog and Gir: That was Skeeter.
Baaulp: Yeah, that was Skeeter.
Wayne: They really named their son Skeeter?
Baaulp: Yeah, and he honks.
Trog: No, it was a nickname.
Gir: Now I do have to get us
back on topic ‘cause Log never
told us what his costume was that he liked.
Trog: Yes, I was just about to say, Log,
do you have costume
stories.
Wayne: Hold on, hold on.
What was Skeeter’s full name?
Trog: I don’t know, look it up.
Baaulp: I don’t know.
Trog: You have Google.
Wayne: Well you’ve failed-you failed the Doug
test. Alright
Log, go ahead.
[Gir laughs]
Baaulp: Doug always called
him Skeeter, which was-which in hindsight
is very funny [laughs].
Wayne: [Laughs] Hey Cummer.
Log: [Laughs] Skeeter Bust.
Wayne, laughing: Skeeter Bust!
Gir: It was Skeeter Valentine!
Trog: Oh yeah, Valentine.
Wayne: Buster Skeeter.
Log: Well anyways,
I only remember three costumes. I was
Winnie-the-Pooh whenever I was two—
Wayne: Aww.
Trog: Wow, surprised you can remember that.
Log: I was Harry Potter
whenever I was five, and I was a
Dementor whenever I was eight.
Trog: Oh, nice.
Wayne: Yooo.
Log: Those are the only costumes I remember.
Trog: You [unintelligible]
Wayne: What was that Dementor costume like?
Log: It was pretty much that-what
you described, the wraith,
but instead of like, a mesh mask it was just
a real ass mask that just kind of looked
like a whirlpool ‘cause they
didn’t have a face, right?
Wayne: Yeah.
Log: They didn’t have red eyes
or anything like that, so I
just wore like, some shitty plastic
to obscure my view. But um, I really
remember that-that Harry Potter time
whenever I was five, because naturally we
all know Harry Potter’s just
fucked beyond belief now—
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: Yeah.
Log: But back then whenever
the first Harry Potter movie
came out, there was so much novel candy
all over the place, like-they had that
one scene with the trolley cart
and just every piece of candy was—
Wayne: They had the chocolate frogs.
Log: Every piece of candy
that was described became real
that Halloween.
Trog: Yeah, that is true.
Wayne: Mhmm.
Gir: Yeah, I remember that.
Log: I ate chocolate frogs,
those fucked up jellybeans were
just widely available, I remember I ate—
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: Fuck those jellybeans.
Wayne: I mean, those are still
available, but they’re just
under a different name now, they
stopped the Harry Potter branding.
Log: Yeah, but they were just
like, they were just very-they
were just everywhere ‘cause I got a hold
of them whenever I was five. I ate an
ear wax jellybean and I could
taste it for like a month.
[Gir laughs]
Baaulp, disgusted: Eeuh.
Log: And I couldn’t stand it.
Trog: I think I had one that
was like, pencil shaving.
Wayne: You remember that those
jellybeans came with like,
trading cards of their like,
teachers? Isn’t that a little weird?
Trog: Yeah. Eh, a little bit, but whatever.
Wayne: Like, you’re at your
own school and you buy some
jellybeans from the lunchroom and you
get a trading card of your math teacher,
who dresses up as Quailman every year.
Trog: [Laughs] Well, that’s not exactly the same—
Gir: But your math teacher’s
not like, world renowned.
Trog: Yeah, it’d be like if
you went to a school where all
of your teachers were incredibly famous
celebrities. Like-like your gym teacher
is Brad Pitt and you get a Brad
Pitt trading card at the lunchroom.
Wayne: That’s true.
Baaulp: That’s still weird!
Wayne: It’s true.
Gir: It’s still weird, but it’s understandable.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: But at least it makes more sense.
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: Oh, that’d be so…
Baaulp: Why were kids in Harry
Potter so dumb? Why’d they
eat candy that tasted bad on purpose?
Trog: Why did kids in real life eat candy
that taste bad on
purpose?
Gir: [Laughs] You fuckin’…
what are you talking about?
Baaulp: I only ate good candy.
Log: Bro, the social studies banner just went up,
I got a five-star
Mrs. O’Neal.
Trog: Hell yeah.
Wayne, laughing: I got a-I got an SR Mrs. Jackson.
[Gir laughs]
Trog: Okay, so now I have an
addendum question that I just
came up with to the costume discussion.
Baaulp: Mhmm.
Trog: Um, you’re transported
back to the ages of ten, but
with your current 2020 adult brain,
what do you pick as your costume?
Baaulp: Power Ranger.
Trog: [Laughs] You don’t change it,
you’re still Power
Ranger?
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: Yeah, dude I mean, if
I go back in time, I’m thinking
like, “Okay, how do I make my
kid self look cool? I mean,
what’s popular right
now"—
Trog: I mean, that’s true.
That’s one way to take it.
Baaulp: Fuckin’, sick ass
Green Ranger costume with
the flute
dagger.
[Baaulp and Wayne sing the
Green Ranger’s summoning song]
Wayne: Uh, CeeLo Green that one time he
dressed up as a
golden man.
[Trog and Baaulp laugh]
Trog: Yeah.
Gir: [Laughs] Just beat him to it.
Wayne: I mean I just want
that costume now, frankly.
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: That—Oh, we should talk
about that later, ‘cause I—Let’s
go around, what are your answers?
Gir: What was popular seventeen years ago?
Trog: Well, let me set the stage. The year is uh,
around let’s
say 1999.
Gir: 1999…
Trog: Uh, I think uh, y’know,
the movie—the Adam Sandler
comedy Big Daddy has taken the world by storm.
Wayne: You were ten in 1999?
Trog: No, I wasn’t.
Wayne: None of us were.
Trog: I don’t know how old everybody is.
Gir: You were six.
Trog: I was six in 1999.
Wayne: If it was 1999—If I was
1999, my costume would be a
large notepad with detailed
instructions on how to thwart 9/11.
[Trog, Gir, and Log laugh]
Trog:
I don’t even want to say
mine anymore, I can’t come up
with anything funnier than that.
[Everyone laughs]
Gir: Uh, Wayne, I’m gonna
go as that, but because I’m
already ten it’s already post-9/11.
Trog: Yeah, fuck, I’m just
gonna go as the lottery numbers,
here you go Mom and Dad.
[Wayne and Gir laugh]
Log: The pressure is on for
your neighborhood, Wayne.
[Wayne and Trog laugh]
Baaulp: Imagine a kid who wakes
up and they’re automatically
already dressed as like a golden golem
and like, etched onto the armor is like,
instructions in English on a terrorist
attack that is yet to happen yet and
just numbers.
Wayne: That’s the greatest story never told.
Trog: That would fuck-like—Imagine
that you’re a parent and
you wake up and your kid starts talking
to you about a terrorist attack, like…
I can’t imagine anything scarier.
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: I mean, they knew about Oo-sama
Bin Laden already,
right?
Gir: Oo-sama.
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: Yeah, so your kid’s
just naming like, political
figures in the Middle East and like,
“Oh, what do we need to do to stop this
event from happening, also here’s
the lottery numbers for this year.”
[Trog and Wayne laugh]
Gir: Hey Baaulp, you know what’s
cool? I recently heard that
uh, time travel’s mathematically
possible because the universe will just
correct itself to what was gonna happen anyway,
so you would—by doing that you
think you’re helping, but you just end up
in a mental hospital and it happens
anyway.
Trog: Damn.
Baaulp: Oh no.
Wayne: I would take precautions, I would act like—
Log: They put the ten-year-old in—
Wayne: Here’s—Here’s how
you do it, you need the core
information of course, how to actually
like, change the exact day, but you also
need information that proves you’re
right. Like, you need extra information
about the future that can be
proven true immediately. Like,
if I know that I’m
going to October—
Log: It needs to go into your Halloween costume.
Wayne: Yes—[laughs].
Gir: You tell them what they were gonna
get you for
Christmas.
Trog: On December 13th, 1999, the movie
Bicentennial man will be released,
and it will get mediocre reviews.
[Gir laughs]
Wayne: Like you just need to
write down and memorize as many
like, stupid little facts about like,
Big Fat Liar and all those movies, like—
[Trog laughs]
Baaulp: When you take me to go
watch the Digimon movie, for some
reason there’s going to be an Angela
Anaconda segment that comes before it.
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: You know what, that’s
perfect, ‘cause who the fuck
would have seen that coming?
Trog: Exactly. It proves you’re
right. This is a great idea
for a movie, I think we should
start a spec script for this.
Wayne: The extra fucked thing
you could do is also like, target
your parents specifically to make sure
you get them on board immediately, and
like tell them information that you know
that they know because they told you
when you were older but didn’t
tell you when you were ten.
Baaulp: Oooh, yeah.
Wayne: Like secrets about their life, or whatever.
Trog: This is scary, this
is like a thriller movie.
Wayne: We could talk about this
for the rest of the podcast,
the uh—
Trog: Yeah.
Gir: Hold on, I just realized
what costume I’d—I would dress
up as one of the kids from Holes.
Baaulp: Why that?
Log: So, like a child prisoner.
Wayne: So, you’re just in an orange jumpsuit
with dirt on
your face.
Gir: I wanna be a prisoner.
Wayne: Hey, I mean that movie was dope back then.
Gir: I wanna eat-I wanna eat canned peaches.
Wayne: I loved Holes.
Trog: It was jarred peaches, I think,
thank you very
much.
Gir: Jarred—Well, shut the
hell up, I don’t know what
containers
are.
Trog: Alright, alright, whatever. Next topic.
Baaulp: Uh, next topic, why did
CeeLo Green dress like that?
I-I think that was after like,
his career went into the dumpster—
Wayne: I mean, that was like his final stunt.
Baaulp: Yeah, that was his final stunt,
was to, “I’m gonna
go as a golem.”
Wayne: He sealed himself in
gold and probably died in the
costume. Like, it’s sad,
but… it was a crazy stunt.
Gir: Yeah, I don’t think he’s
done anything since then.
Trog: I tried looking up, “CeeLo
Green golden golem,” and it
took me to the Dark Souls wiki.
[Wayne, Log, and Baaulp laugh]
Wayne: Oh man, I want a mod that makes Smough
into CeeLo
Green, now.
[Trog laughs]
Gir: Oh, CeeLo Green released two things-or,
he released an
album this year.
Wayne: He made two things, wow.
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: I-y’know, I made more
than two things this year so,
CeeLo Green, step up.
Baaulp: Yeah, same.
Trog: It’s great.
Gir: Baaulp, have you made a hundred things?
Trog: That was last year.
Wayne: Oh, yeah!
Baaulp: I’ve made a hundred things by
now, but I didn’t miss
my—I missed my goal last year.
Wayne: I forgot about that.
Baaulp: I ended up like, with
seventyish things. Turns out
making things is hard.
Gir: Yeah.
Trog; I remember us talking
about our goals for the year and
I immediately forgot mine, so
I think I failed it by default.
Wayne: Who knows. That shit don’t matter.
Baaulp: I mean, no. When we
recorded-we recorded an episode
late 2019 about our New Year’s
resolutions. Mine was to do standup comedy, I
was actually getting the ball rolling on that,
but the problem was, uh, then Covid
happened—
Trog: [Crosstalk] Yeah.
Baaulp: —and there were no
more standup comedy shows, and
now they’re weird because like, a lot of comedians
have like figured out like, “
Yeah we can do them, but they
have to be virtual,” but like, standup comedy is
missing so much when there’s not a live audience,
or like—and you can’t- y’know
like, it-it’s-it’s weird.
Gir: Standup comedy with a virtual audience is
just being a
streamer.
Baaulp: Exactly.
Trog: Kind of.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: I don’t know, I think
there’s something kind of funny
and cosmic about somebody standing on
a stage and telling jokes and like,
pausing for laughter but it
not actually being there.
Gir: Because of the delay.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Gir: Then there’s one person
with a lot of latency, so they
start laughing like, five
minutes after everyone else.
[A moment of silence]
Wayne: [Laughs] Sorry, I
was laughing about Quailman.
Trog: That’s great.
Wayne: Cut that out.
[Trog and Gir laugh]
Baaulp: Alright, I’ll cut that out,
I’ll cut that out, I’ll
fix it in post [laughs].
Wayne: Keep that. That was the
best-that was the best joke
of the episode. Like, do you get it? It’s
delayed laughter, we’re on latency [laughs].
Trog: We should have a “Best
Joke of the Episode” award that
we hand out at the end of each episode.
Baaulp: Hey, that-hey,
honestly? I’ve tried-I’ve tried to
like—‘cause so far this podcast-I mean,
this podcast has had a few episodes,
yeah—
Wayne: [Crosstalk] Has been bad, has sucked.
Baaulp: —We’re really still like,
testing the waters, and I’ve
tried to talk about what segments we
could introduce, and so far this show is
just what we do—we talk, we chitchat
about what we’ve done since last time,
which we can still talk about that, and
then questions. I think a-we—I tried to
introduce a segment where we talk about
how we could get this podcast to be
more popular, but we ran out of ideas,
I like that idea, though. I think we
should have a “Best Joke of the Episode.”
Trog: But the episode’s not over.
Baaulp: What it should be is
we all say a joke right now,
and we have to vote on who wins.
Trog: But it, but—
Wayne: Fuck no.
Log: No.
Gir: Fuck that.
Wayne: I veto this shit.
Baaulp: You veto?
Log: Also, I don’t remember any
of the stuff you said before
that. I don’t remember that ever happening.
Wayne: Like, okay. This concept,
putting us on the spot, say
a joke, and then whoever tells the
best one wins, is like-that’s not—
Baaulp: Say a joke.
Trog: It’s like a nightmare scenario.
It’s like, “Hey, be funny right now.”
Wayne: Yeah.
Log: Bringing the unfortunate like,
social interaction that standup
comedians have to deal with into the online realm.
Trog: Yeah. Do it to your friends.
Gir: Oh, you’re a comedian? Tell me a joke.
Wayne: I have made a name for
myself through comedy, I can’t—You
can’t just tell me to do a joke and I
do one, like I never do that. I would
just say like, “I don’t know,
fuckin’-fart. Get out of my face.”
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: Poop come out of butt, haha.
Baaulp: That’s a pretty good joke.
Trog: It’s all-we’re all—Look. We-we all do
situational
comedy.
Wayne: I guess.
Trog: We all do situational
comedy, we don’t write jokes, we’ve
talked about how we don’t write
jokes on this podcast like, twice.
Baaulp: Oh, yeah.
Log: I’m thinkin’ though, ‘cause
like, yeah. People still do
that, they’ll still like, “Oh, you’re a
comedian? Can you tell me a joke?” What
are they expecting? ‘Cause that’s not
what comedians do now. They don’t just
like-they don’t make like, walks-into-a-bar
jokes or anything like that.
Trog: I mean, it kind of depends on the comedian.
Log: It’s all just about—It’s
like all about their life and
stuff. Like the closest you can get with
like a real-with like a person that’s
alive right now is maybe Demetri Martin
can get you what you need, maybe.
Trog: Yeah, I was about to say,
I was about to name Demetri
Martin as well, like as the one comedian
I can think of that literally just
gets on a stage and just tells jokes. Just
like setup, punchline. Setup, punchline.
Log: But even then, you ambush
him and he doesn’t have a
sketchpad, he doesn’t have a guitar.
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: Yeah, he doesn’t have his guitar.
Baaulp: Yeah, he’s nothing
without that fuckin’ sketchpad.
Log: He’s defenseless.
Trog: I don’t know if anybody—This
is not a slight against
Demetri Martin, Demetri Martin, if
you’re listening to this podcast,
I think you’re
very funny—
Baaulp: Oh yeah, I’m sure.
Trog: —but, I feel like—
Log: Yeah, he’s the only standup comedian
I’ve seen in real
life, he’s cool.
Trog: But I feel like,
um, I feel like nobody’s thought
about Demetri Martin since like, 2009, maybe.
Gir: I have no idea who it is.
Trog: Exactly.
Demetri Martin, come back. Come on our
podcast. You-you should be funny with us.
Wayne: Do you know Eugene Mirman?
Gir: What?
Baaulp and Log: What?
Wayne: Okay, no one knows who Eugene Mirman.
Baaulp: That name sounds familiar.
Wayne: It’s like, it’s some
comedian that like, my older brother
showed me when I was a kid that I
used to think was so fucking funny,
and I remember him vividly for that, and
also because I logged onto his website
and it had something that was borderline
a screamer whenever you logged into
it, and uh, that-that—I wiped whatever
the fuck it was out of my memory.
Trog: It’s-it’s gone now.
Wayne: Yeah, I mean I don’t
want to think about it,
it was
scary.
Gir: The uh, only comedians
I really watched when I was
younger I will not speak of
them as an adult [laughs].
Trog: Yeah. Standup comedy’s
changed. I was just thinking
about the fact that I think my first
exposure to standup comedy were these series
of YouTube videos where somebody just
took like, standup comedy albums, or just
like, individual tracks from standup
comedy albums, and then made them into
like, a Naruto AMV. Like, it’s
not an AMV because it’s not—
Gir: I know exactly what
you’re talking about ‘cause I—
Baaulp: I think I know what
you’re talking about, too.
Trog: Right? Have you guys seen
those? They’re like, so—I’m
talking about, this was like-this was probably
like, 2004. This was like,
early, early, early YouTube.
Gir: ‘Cause I remember specifically like,
Little Tortilla
Boy.
Wayne: What?
Trog: Yeah, there’s like—I don’t
even know who that comedian
is, but I remember that joke.
Gir: That was-I think that was-I
think that was…. Oh, what’s
that dude that’s really
obnoxious and no one likes him…
Trog: Wow, damn. Got him.
Wayne: The one who steals jokes?
Trog: No, it’s not Carlos Mencia.
Gir: No, his deal was he-he
like, did the like, McDonald’s
drive-thru joke.
Trog: Oh, uh, oh! Dane Cook,
I think is who you’re thinking
of. Yeah, Dane Cook.
Gir: Dane Cook! Yeah. Yeah,
I think it was Dane Cook that
did the Little Tortilla Boy joke.
Trog: There was a Dane Cook
one, there was a Dave Chappelle
one, but I-I was just—like it just
dawned on me that, wow, that was my first
exposure to standup comedy were these
ancient YouTube vid—like, Naruto YouTube
videos. It’s so weird to think about.
Gir: I remember that.
Trog: I don’t even like Naru—I
didn’t even watch Naruto as a kid,
but I loved those videos ‘cause of the standup.
Gir: See, okay, it’s funny you
say that because I remember
the same thing, but people did it with
fucking Kingdom Hearts cutscenes. And I don’t
like Kingdom Hearts but I did love those videos!
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: Yeah, like, even
though there was no money to be
made, people wanted to go viral, so when
someone had a good idea people like,
just copied them.
Trog: Yeah, people still do it to this very day.
Baaulp: Yeah. Yup.
Gir: People have done that as long as something
has been popular. If something is popular
someone else wants to do it, too, so they are
popular. That’s just human-the human nature.
Trog: That’s right, I’m calling you out,
Nikola Tesla. You thought you
could invent electricity second?
Wayne: You don’t-no, don’t talk-no,
don’t be mean to him, he
made my cool unicycle.
Trog: Oh, well.
Wayne: Don’t be-do that. Don’t be do that.
Gir: He didn’t make your unicycle.
Wayne: Yes he did his name’s on it! It says
Nikola on it, it
has to be him.
Baaulp: I was a really weird
kid in that like, when most
kids came home from school and watched
cartoons, but at some point after we got
like, basic cable, we had Comedy Central,
and I realized like, wait a minute, there’s
just—I could watch cartoons, but the
only cartoon I cared about watching was
Yu-Gi-Oh! ‘cause it was-it was that era
where like things were starting to get
like, really bad and I like, started not
to care about cartoons anymore, I was
like, wait a minute, I could just come
home after school and there’s just a
channel that has standup comedy, I could
watch that. So I was watching like—They
would air the Chappelle Show, like reruns
of the Chappelle Show and then they
would air like—Comedy Central used to
air a lot of standup, I watched that, I
would watch people’s standup
specials, I was a weird kid.
Wayne: What was the—when
you were a kid, what was the
cartoon that was the breaking point for
you. Where you watched it and you would
like—where you watched it
and you just thought like,
“I’m too old for this now.
Like this is not—”
Baaulp: Oh, like the turning
point where it’s like, oh—
Wayne: The turning point.
Baaulp: I think for me it wasn’t
cartoons, it-for me it was
when Nickelodeon started like
putting more live action—
Wayne: [Crosstalk] Live action.
Gir: Cartoon Network started
doing live action stuff.
Baaulp: It was legitimately,
I think like, Drake & Josh.
Trog: What? Drake & Josh was good!
Wayne: I liked Drake &
Josh. Drake & Josh was good.
Baaulp: I don’t know, I watched it—
Wayne: Here’s the thing, Baaulp.
I’m not saying like-I’m not
saying like, “What? You don’t like
Drake & Josh? You fucking freak! I’m
gonna slam you on the pavement!” Like,
the-like the thing with like, you have a
much stranger history with TV than we do—
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: —like you were watching
Seinfeld at five, so like, it
makes sense that you would step away
from that in a different way than we did,
but I think around the time of
iCarly that is probably when I
also stepped
away.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Gir: I have a twisted sense of television history
as well
because—
Trog: Gir’s a little twisted.
Gir: Between—Fuck you, bitch.
Trog: He’s a little—he’s a little unhinged.
Wayne: A little fucked up.
Gir: Between 2008-between 2008—
Wayne: A little insane.
Gir: Thank you. Between 2008
and 2012 I lived overseas and I
had to watch AFN so I had only like,
fucking, reruns of whatever DVD they had
kicking around in the broadcast studio,
so when I got back to the United States
and saw whatever like, cartoons were again,
it was like, Problem Solverz, and Secret
Mountain Fort Awesome.
Trog: I have no idea what that is, what is that?
Wayne: What the fuck?
Trog: What are you naming?
Log: You don’t remember Problem Solverz?
Trog: No.
Log: Like, that one was notorious.
Wayne: TV makes us all go a
little crazy, huh, MasterGir?
Gir: I was like, “I don’t… think
I like cartoons anymore if this
is what it is, now.”
Log: Yeah, Trog, Google
“Problem Solverz” with a Z.
Trog: Okay.
Wayne: I remember Problem Solverz
because I remember seeing it as like,
it was this weird like, bridge show between
Cartoon Network and Adult Swim, I think they
wanted it to be on Adult Swim but they didn’t
get the okay so they had to tone it down.
Trog: What is this? What is this?
Wayne: Am I-am I right in remembering that
history? Does
anyone else—?
Gir: That sounds right, yeah.
Wayne: Adult Swim would start
at like, eleven and they would
air that show at like, ten-thirty
because they couldn’t quite get it on
Adult
Swim.
Trog: It has the visual style
of like, an Adult Swim show
for sure. That-this is weird, no, I’ve
never heard, never seen this show, this
was like, far past my time, I think.
Gir: But yeah, like
anything-anything between the end of
2011 and like, early 2013 that was on TV
I was like, “I don’t like this. I don’t
think I want to watch cartoons anymore [laughs].”
Log: Around the time that I was
thirteen it was just like, “Alright,
well I don’t have cable in my room anymore,
um, I’m gonna watch Let’s Plays of Silent
Hill 3 and Hitman: Blood
Money now.” And that was it.
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: I remember what killed
it-what killed it for me was
a combination of me already being a weird
kid and I would watch like The Simpsons
and Seinfeld so like, cartoons were like,
the only thing cartoons had were like
how goofy they were, right? ‘Cause
you-‘cause you’d get goofy kid stuff but
then like, once I started getting older
and once like both Cartoon Network and
Nickelodeon were like trying to bridge
the gap and have like live action
programming I was like, “All that, I like
all that, ‘cause it’s goofy and Kenan
Thompson is in a tub, but he’s fully
dressed or y’know, weird shit like that—”
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: But wait, Drake &
Josh is just a show about
people, I don’t care about real people,
if I wanted to watch that I’d watch
Seinfeld, and also I got the Internet,
yeah, I got the Internet so I like, I
just watched like, Let’s Plays and stuff.
Trog: I feel like the breaking
point-the breakoff point where
I stopped caring about cartoons as much is
I feel like-I feel like Teen Titans ended
and I was like, “Cool, I’m done. I
did it. I watched all the cartoons.”
Baaulp: That’s what weaned
you into like, more serious—
Trog: Not even that, because
like honestly, I didn’t even
watch much like, serious adult animation
or anything, I mean like, if you want
to count Family Guy or whatever, sure.
Just because they ran four reruns a day
on Adult Swim.
Wayne: Other than like, iCarly,
like-like it wasn’t that show
specifically, but it was like that era
whenever I got out of it. It was when
Avatar the Last Airbender wrapped up and ended—
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: —and then I was like,
“Okay, I’m done with that, hmm,
these like, episodic, actual stories are
much cooler than like, Fairly OddParents
or whatever the fuck. Um, I’m
gonna get into Dragon Ball Z.”
Baaulp: Yeah, whatever Butch Fartman.
Wayne: And then I got hella into Dragon Ball Z and
I still
think—
Baaulp: Yeahhhh, yeeeeaaaahhhh!
Wayne: And I still think Dragon Ball Z whips ass.
Baaulp: Oh man, there is one
summer as a kid where—they used
to air Dragon Ball Z on Cartoon
Network, like they had an anime block—
Gir: Mhmm yeah, it was called Toonami.
Baaulp and Wayne: Yeah.
Wayne: No, they-they—I feel like before
Toonami they would air Dragon Ball Z.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Gir: Eh-yeah they did.
Wayne: Like, Dragon Ball Z on
Cartoon Network predates that.
Baaulp: And so, like, there was this one summer
where like, for some reason there was a week—It
was brutal, there was a week-almost week
long power outage in my neighborhood like,
it was gross, but there was also a heatwave so my
parents were like, “Alright, what we’re gonna do
is, like, the room that has the most windows is
our living room, we’re gonna put out a mattress
in the living room and we’ll sleep there and you
can sleep on the couch,” ‘cause that is like,
there’s no electricity, right? Like we can’t
turn on the A/C, we can’t turn on the fan,
we just gotta open all the windows and let the
breeze come in. But after the power came back,
they were too lazy to move the mattress
back, and so there was a week and a half
where I would just watch Dragon Ball Z and jump
on a mattress in the living room, it was dope.
[Gir, Wayne, and Log laugh]
Wayne: That’s fucking awesome.
Gir: That reminds me of how uh, my experience
with Dragon Ball as a kid was I saw maybe like
a cou—a handful of episodes that weren’t even in
like, sequence, and was like, “Oh, this is kinda
cool, I kinda like this,” and then fast forward
to like, sophomore year high school like, “Man,
Dragon Ball seems like it’s kind of
popular, I should like actually try to watch
it from start to finish,” and then I
fucking marathoned it, and I’m talkin’
like, did not sleep, twenty-four hours
marathoned all of Dragon Ball Z and by
the end of it I was like, “Oh,
I love this. This is awesome.”
Wayne: For me I—I like saw
an episode here and there of
Dragon Ball Z of like, of the few times
I got to watch Cartoon Network, because
for some reason like—So, I grew up in a
Christian family, but not like diehard
Christian, we were like Protestant and
my mom was like, mostly pretty lax, but
for some reason she—the first time I
watched Cartoon Network I watched Zoids
and my mom saw Zoids and was like, “This
channel’s too violent, you can never
watch this again. You will watch Nickelodeon.”
Gir: Unchristian.
Wayne: Yeah, something about
Zoids was bad, so yeah, I
pretty much didn’t get to watch Cartoon
Network, and the few times that I did I
caught a few episodes of Dragon Ball Z
and I was like, “This is kinda cool,”
and like, I played—and I played Dragon
Ball Z: Budokai and like, I got a lot of
the story from Dragon Ball Z: Budokai
for the first time, and I thought it was
fuckin’ sick and I loved it. That
game was awesome, but not really, but—
Gir: It was when you were a kid.
Wayne: I still have fun playing
it, but it’s a bad game.
Baaulp: When anime hit the west
it hit hard ‘cause it’s like,
somehow like—‘Cause they used to make
like, adventure serials for kids,
and then somehow it turned into only
comedy and only slapstick, and then like—
Gir: They followed the money.
Baaulp: And then anime hit,
and it’s like, “Woah, what is
this shit? It’s like, this isn’t funny,
this is just serious, but it’s for kids
like me!”
Wayne: So yeah, I-I got into
it through that, and then when
I was in middle school I was like, I
was moving on from cartoons, but I would
still watch some Family Guy and there
was also a channel called Nicktoons
Network where they would air like, the
shows that got cancelled, it was an
interesting like, channel in general but,
they aired-they announced like, “Coming
soon to Nicktoons Network, Dragon Ball
Z Kai,” and I’m like, “Wow, this looks
like, much cleaner than it used to, and
this looks really cool,” and I watched
that, and I watched that weekly and it
was fuckin’ awesome. So, I actually got
the full experience of Dragon Ball Z
up to some point in the Cell Saga like,
watching it bi-weekly as if I had actually
been keeping up with the releases,
it was fuckin’ dope.
Gir: Y’know, that reminds me,
I want—I’m gonna reel it back
once again to Halloween. That reminds
me of my favorite Halloween memory of
going out trick-or-treating, blah blah
blah, you know all that fun stuff you
usually do on Halloween, then coming
home, turning off all the lights so people
don’t try to get candy from us
‘cause we didn’t have any for them—
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: —and then turning on the
TV and watching the Nicktoons
Network Animation Film-Animated
Film Festival. I feel like
I’ve told this story
before—
Wayne: I remember that! Yeah.
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: I also remember around
Halloween time Nickelodeon would
have like, these like bumpers between episodes
of their shows that were like, genuinely
scary, like, I don’t-I don’t remember
much about them, but I bet someone out
there does, where it was like this—It
was a dual tone like, color scheme, it
was literally just orange and black, and
there was this weird like, short dude
with long arms just like talking about
like, “[In a deep voice] Uh, there’s you
know—Do you like scary stories? There’s
one kind and then there’s the other
kind.” And then like just a bloody sawblade
would appear or something like that
and it was fuckin’ strange and
uncharacteristic for Nickelodeon.
Gir: I don’t remember that.
Wayne: It scared the shit out of me.
Trog: No, I think you’re imagining this.
Wayne: No, it’s definitely real.
Log: Legend of Sleepy Hollow,
Headless Horseman slashin’
through your screen!
Wayne: Nope, nope. [Laughs]
Cutting through your selfies!
Gir: Do you remember Prometheus and Bob?
Baaulp: Yes.
Trog: Mhmm.
Gir: Fucking loved Prometheus and Bob.
Wayne: No.
Gir: You don’t?
Wayne: I don’t know what that is.
Baaulp: I loved KaBlam!.
Gir: Fucking KaBlam! was so good.
Wayne: What the fuck—Okay, now
y’all are just making up things.
Didn’t-didn’t you love Alien and George?
[Log laughs]
Gir: I mean, that’s what it was!
It was an alien and a caveman!
Baaulp: KaBlam! was a variety show.
Gir: Yeah.
Baaulp: It was like-it was
like a sketch variety show, but
it—This is why like, Nickelodeon was
cool. It was a sketch variety show that
was a mix of animation, and live action,
and Claymation, it was like all
animated in different ways, but it
was a sketch variety show, and Prometheus
and Bob was just like, a slapstick,
almost Tom and Jerry-esque show like,
little segment they’d have and it was
hilarious as a kid because like, Prometheus
was this alien that was desperately trying
to teach this caveman like, advanced
concepts and like, it’s slap-it’s like
slap—it’s like a different dynamic than
say like, Tom and Jerry where like,
they’re enemies like, the alien is genuinely
trying to help the caveman and the caveman
just doesn’t get it and like, fucks
everything up and it was hilarious.
Gir: And there was-and there
was a monkey that would fuck
things up, too, ‘cause the monkey was smarter.
Wayne: Y’all remember the
Nickelodeon show that like, to me,
all memories of it feel like a
fever dream, that was about like,
a naked action
figure?
Trog: That was part of KaBlam!.
Gir: I think that was Action Team Now?
Wayne: That was part of KaBlam!?
That’s why-that’s why it
came to my memory, I guess.
Trog: It was either Action Team or Action League,
something like
that.
Gir: Action League.
Wayne: That shit was weird,
I don’t remember shit about
that. There were many things that scared
me when I was akid that shouldn’t, I
remember that show just, making
me like vaguely upset, like,
whenever I watched
it.
[Trog laughs]
Baaulp: Really?
Wayne: Just this weird sense
of discontent. It was strange.
Trog: It was just like, not Claymation,
but it was stop motion
action figures.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: It was stop motion of these weird, naked—
Gir: It was part stop motion
and part like, toys on strings.
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: Yeah, them just dragging toys around.
Wayne: Was there other characters
than the naked guy? I only
remember the naked guy.
Baaulp: There was a Wonder Woman
equivalent, and then there
was Stinky Diver.
Trog: I remember that, I remember Stinky Diver.
What a good
name.
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: Wayne, you’re thinking of
The Flesh. He’s quote, “Super
strong and super naked.”
Trog and Wayne: Yeah.
Wayne: It’s coming back to me now.
Gir: He has Thunder Girl, “She flies
like thunder,” Stinky Diver, “A former
Navy commando who has an attitude—with
an attitude as bad as his odor,” uh,
Meltman, my favorite, “With the power to… melt!”
Trog: Oh, yeah.
Log: You guys can watch your dumb-dumb shows—
[Baaulp laughs]
Log: I was watching fuckin’ Cubix.
[Trog and Baaulp laugh]
Wayne: Fuck you. Fuck you, bitch.
Gir: Fuck you and your trash.
Trog: Log was all in on those-on
those Korean animations.
Log: Yo, man, I discovered so
many secret shows as a five
year old, like I was watching
Cubix, I was watching .hack//Sign.
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: What? You were watching .hack at five?
Log: I didn’t know what .hack//Sign
was—Yeah! ‘Cause it came
on at like, 2AM, like sometime—
Wayne: Don’t people get—You
were up at 2AM at five?
Trog: Why were you up at 2AM?
Log: Whenever I was a little kid like,
sometimes over—like sometime-like
you don’t have to go to school sometimes,
right? So it was like, “Whatever, it’s
Saturday,” sometimes I’m just in the living
room, sleeping on the couch ‘cause five
year olds want to sleep on the couch
sometimes, and I look at the TV and it’s like,
“Oh! What’s this? It’s about video games,
man I wish I knew what video game
this was, I would play it.”
[Baaulp, Trog, and Wayne laugh]
Gir: I will say because my
parents didn’t really pay too
much attention or really care all too
much what I was watching on TV, as like a
six or seven-year-old I was watching South Park.
Baaulp: When I was a kid, the
thing that I always tried to
stay up to watch but never could ‘cause I
would always get too tired and fall asleep
were like—I really like the
Conan O’Brien show. But it—
Gir: You’re so weird.
Baaulp: But it came on so late
that I like always passed out.
Like, I would see—I remember my cousin
showing me clips of it and like, I guess
he had like DVDs or something and
it was like, man, I thought it
was really
funny.
Wayne:
Happy Halloween! It’s time for scary questions.
Ooouuuhhhh!
[An assortment
of scary sounds are made by the crew]
Wayne: Guys, I got hooked you gotta unhook me.
Trog and Gir: I don’t get it.
[Gir and Wayne laugh]
Wayne:
If you want to ask us questions that
will be answered on the Where Do We
Begin podcast that you are listening
to right now, there are two ways to
do it. You can join the WayneRadioTV
Discord server, discord.gg/wayneradiotv,
we don’t even need some crazy URL that we
have to put in the description anymore,
I can say it to you right now. Or, you can email
us at wheredowebeginqa@gmail.com, where you can
send us questions and get—if-if you email them
you get-you get your questions put on a pedestal.
Baaulp: They still have to be
good, though. They still have
to be good.
Log: And they still have to be questions.
Wayne: Yes, you still have to follow our rules.
Baaulp: I’m the
one that checks the email account and man,
we got—you gotta-the email, the few emails we get,
they gotta be better. Just
sayin’.
Trog: I feel like we may have
actually answered this before
on the podcast, so stop me if we’ve
already done this one, ‘cause I literally
all-all memories of the podcast leave
my brain as soon as we stop recording,
but we have a question here from Blue
who says, “If you were a clown, what
would your clown name be and
what’s your special trick?”
Wayne: Well we definitely
haven’t answered that before.
Baaulp: Yeah, I think that one’s new.
Wayne: I already answered both
these questions—parts of this
question on my stream last night, my
clown name would be PenisFuck and I
would have
a monkey.
Gir: That would be your special
trick? Is have a monkey?
Baaulp: I mean that counts, yeah.
Wayne: I’m a monkey clown.
Trog: Your trick can’t just be, “Has a monkey.”
Wayne: Well no, I have a monkey clown and I
do tricks with a
monkey.
Trog: Yeah, what is it?
Wayne: Like we juggle together, and I make him
do dances. And
I—He—
Trog: What’s your-what’s
your—Okay, you-you are PenisFuck
the monkey clown. What is your grand finale
trick that like, leaves everyone stunned?
Wayne: Uh, the monkey pretends to murder me.
[Trog and
Baaulp laugh]
Gir: Alright!
Wayne: We got-we got-we got
like squibs-we got like squibs
and everything. Like he bites my neck,
and I’m wearing like a big clown collar,
right? But he bites the neck and the
squibs under there and it fuckin’ explodes.
Baaulp: A big-a big clown collar?
Wayne: Yeah! You know what
a clown collar looks like!
Trog: This is like a setup for
a CSI episode where it’s like—
Baaulp: The monkey actually kills you!
Trog: —“Oh yeah, this clown
always did a trick where he gave
his monkey a gun with blanks in it, but
this time somebody replaced the blanks
with real bullets.”
Wayne: That is also great.
A monkey with a gun full of
blanks is like the funniest
thing a man could think of, like—
[Trog, Baaulp, and Gir laugh]
Wayne: Now if you could arrange that—that
that gun could have infinite blanks somehow,
that would be amazing. Just a fuckin’
macaque runnin’ around your town like,
trying to do monkey run-bys on people, and
like—Oh man, it’d be so good, so funny.
Gir: Alright, my clown name is
uh, the children all scream.
If they want to address me, all
the children have to scream.
Trog: Ah, I see, so it’s sort of like—
Gir: Okay?
Trog: —less of something that
you can write down and more of
like, a vibe.
Gir: Yeah, and then my special
trick is if the parents want
the kids to stop screaming,
they have to pay extra.
Trog: That’s a pretty good trick.
Wayne: That’s not a trick-that’s
not pretty—that’s not very
funny, that’s not very funny for like, a clown.
Trog: No, it’s not a funny
trick, but it is a-it is a—
Gir: Nobody said the clown had to be funny.
Wayne: It’s a lucrative—
Trog: It’s a lucrative trick.
Gir: [Laughs] It’s a lucrative trick.
Wayne: Why would anybody hire
this clown? Shouldn’t—Aren’t
you supposed to disclose that kind of stuff.
Trog: [Crosstalk] Because they don’t know.
Gir: They don’t know.
Log: You can’t advertise as this clown,
so it doesn’t
matter.
Wayne: I almost feel like any parent
that’s getting their kid a clown for
their birthday party isn’t gonna check
shit, like they just need a clown.
Gir: No, yeah, exactly.
Log: I got a clown name last
night, too. Uh, I’m PenMaster
and I would do like, magic tricks with
drawings. So they’d give me big easel and
you can draw pictures on the page and
it’d probably have a little trick in it
that lets you move the paper.
Wayne: That actually—that’d be pretty cool.
Log: There’s probably
a clown that does that already. Probably.
But I’m just guessin’ off the top of my head.
Wayne: Mhmm.
Trog: Uhh—
Wayne: They call him The Magic Pens.
Trog: I couldn’t come up with
a good answer off the top of
my head, so whenever I don’t know how
to answer a question like this, my first
thing is always to turn to software to
help me. So I opened up AI Dungeon and I
said, “You are a clown named—” and it
said, “You are a clown named The Clown.”
So that’s it.
[Wayne laughs]
Log: You are a clown named Software.
Wayne: I mean, hey, I think if that’s your
name, like, you-you draw two traits. You’re
not memorable, but you have some balls. Like,
you have the balls to name yourself like,
“Yeah, I’m The Clown. I am the
titular, singular, specific clown.”
Trog: Yeah. I am The Clown.
And uh, my special trick is…
Wayne: Got that air of confidence.
Trog: My special trick is…
I throw a pie in your face and
your pants fall down.
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: That’s not nice!
Trog: No, it’s not.
Wayne: There’s like a-like
a—What are those call-what are
they called, bolas? There’s like fuckin’
bolas that swing at your pants along
with the pie and pull them down.
Gir: Trog I love that like—You say that like
it’s guaranteed to make your
pants fall down every time.
Trog: Oh, yeah. That’s why it’s
like—It’s the special trick.
Gir: That’s why it’s a special trick, yeah.
Trog: Yeah. It makes your
pants fall down no matter what.
Gir: “What the fuck? I had a
belt on!” “What the hell, I was
wearing suspenders!” “What the
hell, I wasn’t even wearing pants!”
Wayne: Makes your pants
disappear. I mean, then we’re in
more of like, magician territory
than clown. When you affect others.
Baaulp: My… clown name would
be-would be—I think-I think I
would use the one from last
night. Flower Squirt, and—
Gir: You have a flower that squirts.
Baaulp: My trick is I have Spiderman web shooters.
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: Are they shaped like flowers?
Baaulp: No—I mean, yes.
Trog: What do you do with them?
Wayne: I mean the joke is that
he’s just more like Spiderman
than a clown, and it’s not quite right, so—
Trog: [Laughs] Yeah.
[Gir laughs]
Wayne: It’s very funny.
Gir: I do like the idea of someone
coming to like, a party like,
“Hey, I’m the clown!” And they’re just
completely dressed like Spiderman.
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne: That’s a good—That is
actually a good clown bit.
Trog: They don’t know what
a clown or Spiderman is.
Wayne: That element would
confuse the kids, but it’d be
funny for the parents.
Trog: Yeah.
Gir: “Why are you dressed like
Spiderman?” “Oh, ‘cause it’s
funny, I’m a clown!”
Wayne: “I’m sort of like a high
concept, like avantgarde, absurdist
clown, like I’m gonna do some things that
are going to make you guys laugh, your
kids don’t know what the fuck’s
gonna go on, like-you’re gonna—”
Gir: “Listen to your kid, I’m the people’s clown,
I do what’s
funny to me.”
Wayne: No, then you’re not the people’s clown.
Log: I’m an open source clown.
Wayne: You have a selfish-you’re a selfish clown.
Gir, laughing: Shut up, kid!
Wayne: I’m twenty-fwive.
Log: If you upload it to GitHub I’ll do ‘em.
[Trog laughs]
Gir: Twenty-fwive!
Wayne: [Laughs] I’m also not twenty-five,
I don’t know why I
like—
Trog, laughing: You just—That
is like, entirely incorrect.
Wayne: It’s like-it’s incorrect, but just slightly
incorrect enough that it doesn’t make any sense.
Like, it’s not like I said like I’m forty,
I’m not doing a joke like I’m older than I am.
It’s just wrong, like my brain failed.
Trog: Uh, we have a question here
from Discord user, ArthurLovesYou,
who says, “If you absolutely had to
get a tattoo, what would you get?”
Wayne: I thought about this
many times. Because the concept
of a tattoo I love, but I don’t know
what the fuck—I can’t never decide.
Trog: It’s a really daunting decision.
Baaulp: This is why I don’t have a tattoo now,
because like-like ever since like—Y’know I feel
like the idea of tattoos being cool kinda starts
to creep in in high school. Like high school is
when I remember my friends going like, “Yeah,
what if I got a tattoo?” And that just like,
is a concept to you now. But like, I think
about it—I’m like, I like a lot of things,
there’s nothing I like that much that I would
throw down money for an artist to etch on my body.
Gir: It’s true.
Baaulp: Y’know-you know what
I mean? Like, I like Pokem—
Gir: That’s exactly how I feel.
Baaulp: For example,
um, there’s a kid that really liked
sailing, and so they had like a
sailing sextant tattooed—They were like, “Ooh,
what if I got a sextant tattooed on me,” I’m like,
I don’t think I—Y’know. Or I
met a guy who like, really liked
Pokemon, so they had Squirtle tattooed on
them, y’know? It’s like y’know, whatever,
y’know, like some people are so
casual about it, but I’m here like,
I would not do that! Like, I like so many
things but there’s nothing that I—
Wayne: Baaulp. I’ve got you
pinned, I’ve got you cornered.
Baaulp: What would I get? What would I get?
Wayne: You would get a tattoo of the Cupman from
Neverwinter
Nights.
Baaulp: …No! I don’t want that etched on my
body! Here’s the
thing, like—
[Trog and Wayne laugh]
Gir: Yeah, what are you talking
about? He likes that, but—
Baaulp: Would I—Okay, would I
get Cupman on a shirt? Yes. Would
I get Cupman on a cake and then eat it? Yes.
Wayne: Yakuza-style back tattoo of the Cupman.
Full back
tattoo.
Baaulp: Would I get like,
a Cupman—Would I get a Cupman
decal on my car? Yes. But I would not get Cupman
etched on my body ‘cause that
seems stupid.
Wayne: What if it’s like extremely
funny and not public facing?
Like, would you get a Cupman tattoo
on your ass that no one sees? But
you can
say that.
Gir: That would be kind of
funny, actually [laughs].
Trog: But then if somebody does see it,
it’s going to be even more confusing.
Baaulp: I still-I still wouldn’t
want that. I still wouldn’t
want that.
Trog: Can I suggest another
one for you, Baaulp? Because
whenever Wayne started suggesting a tattoo
I thought he was going to take it in
this direction. I think you should
just get a chicken wing somewhere.
Baaulp: Uhhh… I don’t know…
Trog: You do love chicken wings.
Wayne: See, you run the risk—You
have to have this balance
of both importance and also like,
the fact that it would look good.
Trog: And also that it’s on
you until you want to get it
painfully removed.
Wayne: You don’t want to be
like that one redhead dude that
I can’t remember the name of—I think his
name’s like—Ed Markey’s what’s coming
to my head, but I kn—That’s the politician.
The fuckin’-the fuckin’ annoying
singer who has a fucking like Heinz
ketchup bottle tattooed on his arm, like
you don’t want to end up like that.
Trog: That’s some Coach McGuirk shit.
Wayne: What is his name? You know his name.
Trog: I have no idea who you’re talking about.
Wayne: The redhead guy! The redhead
guy who looks a little goofy.
Baaulp: The guy!
Wayne: And he makes boring music.
Trog: What are you talking about?
Baaulp: That’s a lot of people, bro.
Trog: The redhead—Oh, oh!
Fuck, no, I know who you’re
talking about, but I don’t know
his name, either. It’s a musician.
Wayne: Why the fuck can’t we remember who this is?
Baaulp: ‘Cause we don’t listen to pop!
Gir: He’s unmemorable!
Trog: I don’t know—Is it Ed
Sheeran? Is it Ed Sheeran?
Wayne: Ed Sheer—[Claps once]
It is Ed Sheeran, you got it.
Trog: That’s who it is.
Wayne: I don’t know why-I
couldn’t think anything but Ed
Markey, and I know who Ed Markey is.
Trog: Yeah, Ed Sheeran has a
fucking ketchup bottle tattooed
on like he’s Coach McGuirk from Home Movies.
[Wayne and Log laugh]
Wayne: Honestly, getting a
BabyBel cheese cow tattoo would
be like, a fucking great tattoo.
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: Gotta love that cheese.
Wayne: I’m not even-I’m not even the
biggest Home Movies fan,
and that would be great.
Trog: I’m sure so many people have that, like—
Wayne: Unlike-unlike Baaulp, who said like,
Baaulp was like, “ I don’t really like-I don’t
love a piece of media enough to like, engrave
that onto me,” I am an independent being who
thinks for themselves, and is understanding of
like the downsides of media and what they play
in our lives. However, I do love myself some
media. But I am of the concern of like, if
you’re gonna get a tattoo from like a video game
or a movie or an anime or something like that,
it cannot be like, super easily recognizable
because then it’s like-it just fuckin’ blows.
Like-like I would not get a tattoo of just
like, a picture of Goku on my arm, although—
Trog: So you’d get the Triforce, right?
Wayne: Saying that out loud,
that would be pretty funny. Like,
just Goku. Just concept art of
Goku like, the basic reference art.
Trog: That’d be an expensive tattoo.
Wayne: Yeah. For me, if it’s a
reference to something, like,
it has to be very cool in itself, and
I’ve only ever had one idea that I’ve
been like, close to doing, but the thing
that holds me back is that like, it is
too elaborate and I feel like it could
get fucked up and not be good. I think a
really cool tattoo from an anime would
be Scar’s destruction arm from Full
Metal Alchemist: Brotherhood,
like the engravings on his arm.
Trog: That’d be cool. Yeah.
Wayne: Yeah, like that would
be sick. But the two things I
need in order to pull that off: I need
to find a really good tattoo artist, and
I need to get buff. I-I don’t
earn it if I’m not buff.
Trog: And you have to always
wear a cloak so that like, you
can whip it out and threaten people with it.
Wayne: And I have to kill
any alchemists that I see.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: [Laughs] I have to kill all alchemists.
Trog: You have to be really threatening with it.
Gir: I’ve thought about it before, ‘cause I could
literally get one tomorrow if I wanted because my,
uh, my mom is like a tart—tartoo—tattoo
artist, and I think if anything—‘Cause
I’m with Baaulp, there’s nothing that I
really like enough that I want-I want it
etched onto my body—but I think I would
probably get the Turtle School symbol.
Trog: Not a bad one.
Wayne: Where? On your chest or on your back?
Gir: No—Like, on my back,
on my shoulder blade, maybe.
Wayne: Like a full back size?
Trog: On both of my palms.
Gir: No, no! On my shoulder blade!
Wayne: Oh.
Baaulp: Are you sure you wouldn’t
want a third eye on your
forehead like Tien [laughs]?
Trog: [Laughs] That would be sick.
Wayne: Now that’d be dope.
That would be sick. You will
actually be able to do Tri-Beams
if you do that. Just so you know.
Trog: Yeah, nobody’s ever
tried it before because they’re
too scared.
[Wayne laughs]
Log: Maybe you should tattoo your skin green.
Trog: Just like Piccolo.
Gir: No.
Baaulp: Oh, yeah.
Gir: ‘Cause I knew a guy, he
used to work at the place I
worked, uh, but he would still come
in a lot, and he had-he had one arm
completely dedicated to Halo tattoos.
Baaulp: Oh my god.
Wayne: That’s fuckin’ sick.
That-that is so lame and so sick
at the same time. I love that.
Gir: It was pretty cool. If
it was lame I wouldn’t have
brought it up, but he had like
a big ass energy sword on there,
he had like the
legendary—
Wayne: It’s lame in the good way.
Gir: Mhmm.
Wayne: Like, that’s so cheesy. I love it.
Baaulp: For me it’s about
execution. Like if the art is
legitimately good—
Gir: It was good art.
Baaulp: —and if-if-if it’s like your
full arm, then it wraps
around to being cool.
Gir: It was the full arm, too. Yeah.
It was the full arm, he
had like a big ass Master Chief
on there, he had like the legendary difficulty
logo, he had like, he had all kinds of shit on
there, it was pretty tight,
actually.
Wayne: There’s another kind of
tattoo that I would want but
I can’t get because it’s not okay—Like,
a genuine yakuza-style back tattoo
would be fucking awesome, but like,
it’s not good to do that, like, for
multiple reasons why you can’t do that.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Gir: You can’t-you can’t
visit Japan if you do that.
Log: Yeah, you’d get—You’d get into a battle.
Wayne: You can’t visit Japan,
that-that means bad things in
Japan, and also like, it is-I think
it is appropriation, in a way, the-you
shouldn’t do that. But it looks so
cool. Those fuckin’-those fucking
flowing back tattoos onto
the arms are so fucking sick.
Log: The street thugs would get at you if you
were wearing
that tattoo.
Wayne: Every—Yeah, every
five minutes walking down the
street four men in suits would come out
and try to—They would challenge me to a
fight, and they would take turns
throwing punches at me in a circle.
Baaulp: And then a giant
eight-foot man would like,
slam you
on the ground.
Wayne: [Laughs] Rips all
the money out of your pants.
Baaulp: Yeah, all the money
in your checking account
would
disappear.
[Wayne laughs]
Log: Yeah, I wouldn’t really
want a tattoo. I think if I had
to get one I’d want one that would
look like just a weird-like an abstract
photoshop project. Like, just take
standard images but have them to where it
looks like they’re just like
cleanly separated, y’know? Like,
y’know what I’m
talking about?
Gir: No.
Baaulp: Yeah, like you want something abstract—
Log: The box will—Like Box
Select like part of it, and then
like, move it away so that it’s
like the full thing is there but
it’s like
separated.
Gir: That could be cool.
Log: I feel like that could
be—I feel like that could look
kinda cool.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Log: Uh, either that or just
like-like a shitty rubber boot
that you would get by fishing
in a river or something.
[Trog laughs]
Log: But just like the line
art of it, and really small.
Gir: I think like a little
rubber boot on like a hook and
line could be—
Log: Nah, no hook and line, just like a boot.
Gir: Just a shit boot? Would you like, put that on
like your
ankle?
Log: Nah, just anywhere.
Gir: On your palm.
Log: Yeah.
[Gir laughs]
Log: Put a boot on my palm.
Baaulp: [Sighs] I-I
legitimately—Okay, the one thing I can
think of, like—The way I see tattoos is
like, you gotta really—It’s gotta like
really mean something to you. It’s gotta be—
Gir: Oh!
Baaulp: It’s gotta like
really, really mean something
to you, y’know what I mean? Like—
Gir: Yeah, I-I actually—
Baaulp: I’ve always grown
up thinking about that—What?
Gir: I have a suggestion for you, Trog.
Trog: [Laughs] Sure, what is it.
Gir: Uh, Marshie the Marshmallow.
Trog: Oh my god, no, that’s-that would be…
[Gir and Baaulp laugh]
Wayne: A Homestar Runner tattoo
would be pretty good. I’d
definitely get a Homestar tattoo
if I could think of the right one.
Trog: I’m-I’m with Log in that
I do not ever foresee myself
ever getting a tattoo. Part
of that comes from my uh,
incredible fear of
needles, but—
Baaulp: Oh, yeah.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: —the other part of it comes from
the fact that I-I legitimately like—I
mean, I like a lot of media, but I don’t know if I
like anything, anything, enough to like permanent—
Baaulp: Yeah, that’s the thing—
Trog: —well, not permanent,
but y’know like, essentially
permanently add it to me.
Like it becomes part of me.
Baaulp: Yeah. That’s exactly
like—I’ll buy it, I’ll buy a
poster, I’ll frame it, I’ll have the
art in my home, I’ll buy-I’ll play the
game, I’ll buy—I’ll eat fuckin’-I’ll
eat the fuckin’ fruit snacks! But like,
you-If you’re like, “Okay, etch this
onto your skin,” that like, crosses some
line in my head where it’s like, “No,
I don’t want something like that,”
y’know. And like it being permanent has
nothing to do with it, right? ‘Cause if
I’m buying a poster I want it in my
home, but it’s like, it being on my skin
it’s like-I don’t need it to go that far.
Trog: I would-so I would get—So if I was
forced to and I can’t just pick like a
cop-out like, “Oh I get a dot on my ankle,”
or whatever, like it has to be a real tattoo,
I wanna go all in and I just wanna get the exact
tattoos from the movie Memento all over my body—
Baaulp: Ohhhh fuck.
Trog: —so that I can walk around
in public and then pretend
to have amnesia and start freaking out
and then take my clothes off and look at
all of my tattoos and then calm down.
Baaulp: Nice.
Gir: Consider this about your
fear of needles, uh, that
needle stabs you so fast you can’t even see it.
Trog: I know.
Wayne: Invisible needles.
Trog: No, legitimately I just
wouldn’t want to get a tattoo
because I just can’t think of
anything good enough. If I can
think of something
good enough—
Wayne: The Covid vaccine will be invisible!
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: So that it doesn’t scare Trog [laughs].
Trog: If I-if I-if I could
think of something cool enough
that I like—Y’know, honestly, what came
to my mind, but I probably wouldn’t do
this because this would be like-it would
have to be a big tattoo to work and I
wouldn’t want like a big tattoo, is like,
I kind of would get—maybe think about
getting like the fucking Amiga
Juggler somewhere on my body—
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: —just because I feel
like that’s like just obscure
enough but within my realm of things I
think are quaint and neat that like I
could maybe see that, but that
would be a really obscure thing
to get tattooed
on your body.
Wayne: Y’know-y’know what would
be a good spot for like a funny
tattoo? Would be like right at the top
of your spine on the back of your neck—
Trog: Oh my god.
Wayne: Like it just creeps out from
behind a shirt collar,
so someone-someone—
Gir: Right where it would hurt the most.
Trog: I was about to say, that would hurt so bad.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: Yeah, yeah. But
someone-someone walking behind you
would like, just get this-the
little juggler popping out.
Trog: Yeah, they get a little peak.
Wayne: [Laughs] Yeah.
Baaulp: I’ll give you one
scenario I can see myself getting
a tattoo is—And there’s like a precedent
for this in like, I think certain
places in Asia, I remember watching a
video from a documentary about it, this
like-they do this in Southeast Asia I
think, but like, practitioners, like, if
you’re a practitioner of a specific style
of animal Kung Fu, like Tiger style,
or Mantis style, you get that animal
tattooed on you, and that’s what I’d do.
If I was like, “I’m gonna try Tiger
style Kung Fu,” and I like, find myself
getting really good at it, I would get
a tiger tattooed on me. ‘Cause then it
wraps around to like, this means
something. And it’s also badass.
Wayne: But it’ll never be as
cool as a yakuza back tattoo.
Gir: No, you get-you do Snake
style so you have like the
snake that wraps around
your arm and then you like—
Wayne: That is actually dope.
Gir: Have it on the side of
your hand so you can open your
hand and it’s like the snake opens its mouth.
Wayne: Yeah, if you have
like—Honestly, the concept of like-like
a snake wrapped around your back
and it turns into your hands,
that’s pretty
fuckin’ rad.
Baaulp: But like, that’s an
example of the kind of devotion
I would have to have in something for me
to be like, “Yeah, it’s a good idea to
get a tattoo,” like, oh I’m a
practitioner of this martial art.
Wayne: Get a tattoo of Bob from Tekken.
Baaulp: That’s a video game!
Wayne: Yeah, but you’re a
practitioner of that martial art
and you’ve-you’ve dedicated thousands
of hours of your life to playing as Bob.
Gir: You do have speed and weight.
Wayne: See? You see what I’m sayin’.
Baaulp: But that’s so lame, ugh.
Wayne: Final answer for me,
another-another good tattoo idea
that just requires the right word—Knuckle
tatts with a word. I like-we’ve—Log
had that fucking hilarious idea a long
ass time ago where it’s like, the best
knuckle tattoo says, “Bonus
Fingers,” and you have extra fingers.
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: [Laughs] Yeah, I think about that a lot.
Baaulp: Have a Tiger style—Like,
have a tiger right next to
your Heinz ketchup bottle to symbolize
that you like ketchup and you’re
a practitioner of Tiger style.
Wayne: Uh, okay, I really like
this question from tyefyedie,
which is, “What’s something you’ve come
across the Internet that you’ve tried
to find again, but have been
unable to find it at all?”
Trog: Oooh.
Wayne: Whether it’s you just
simply lost it, or you think it
got removed and you can’t find any archive of it—
Gir: “Rebuild the Internet, Andy!”
Trog: That’s gone.
Wayne: That’s one, that’s our conjoined answered.
Gir: “Rebuild the Internet!”
Wayne: Our conjoined answer
is the uh, this video of this
man filming himself in a mirror, uh,
he’s unkempt and bearded, and uh, he—
Gir: Shirtless.
Wayne: Was he shirtless?
Trog: Yes.
Gir: He was shirtless.
Trog: He was definitely.
Wayne: He was standing in a
mirror filming himself and he
was just babbling on about inventing the
Internet and the iPhone and specifically
he was like, “Andy, this is Steve Jobs
talking to you! Rebuild the Internet,
Andy! Rebuild the Internet! I bet you
seventy-five fucking cents you cannot rebuild
the Internet, Andy! This is Steve Jobs
talking to you!” And he just progressively
gets louder and louder and it
was like one of the best videos.
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: And nobody saved it. ‘Cause we’re stupid.
Gir: “Take the bet, kid!”
Wayne: “Take the bet!” Yeah,
I forgot about that part.
[Gir laughs]
Wayne: The last time I brought
this up was during the Half Life:
Alyx stream and someone was like, “You
just need to recreate that, Wayne,” and
I was like, yeah-why the fuck—
Trog: It’ll never be the same.
Gir: It won’t.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: I can get pretty close.
I mean, it won’t be the same,
but archives the concept.
Gir: ‘Cause you’re not a lunatic talking to
themself in a
mirror!
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: That’s the thing, is it
loses the authenticity factor
that that guy was saying that, fully
believing it-whatever he was saying.
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: My lost media thing,
I actually found again!
Trog: Well then it’s not lost.
Wayne: Well then it’s not-well then
it’s not part of this question!
Baaulp: Huh, well alright…
Gir: It’s true. Sorry, Baaulp.
Wayne: You found it, you found it,
so it’s not the right
answer.
Baaulp: Okay, alright, who’s next?
Wayne: I’m just-you can talk about it,
but I had to drill
you on that for fun.
Baaulp: [Laughs] For the long—When I was
a kid, y’know every kid is gonna watch
like-that grew up in the same era as me, watched
Flash animations, and like it was slim pickings,
you took what you could get, and for some
reason, this wasn’t even meant for kids,
it was meant for adults—Not in that it was
an adult subject matter, it was a cooking
show. It was a cooking show that was animated
in Flash, and not only was it a cooking show,
it was a cooking show that was like, where the
premise was there was a fake talk show—This was
something that would have gone over my head
so much, but I loved it, I love hearing about
the merit of Old Bay Seasoning and how to use
it for your seafood dishes, and how to deep
fry chicken and this and that. It was like,
what the fuck is this show. And it also like,
was hosted by a cartoon octopus and I found it-it
probably hasn’t aged well because it’s like what,
a cooking show from 2005 animated in Flash
that had like five episodes? I have no idea
who made these or like what their end goal was
because I can’t imagine them getting a lot of
money out of this. It was probably like some
kitchenware company, I don’t know, but it was
called Deep Fried LIVE with Tako the Octopus.
What the fuck. But I found it, so that’s cool.
Gir: I can’t think of anything
beyond that “rebuild the
Internet”
video.
Trog: Yeah, I don’t know. I’m
trying to think of anything
that I would’ve saw as a kid, but I feel
like anything I saw as a kid, like I
can still get it, like I can still find it.
Gir: Wait are we talking about
as a kid or just in general?
Log: In general.
Gir: Okay.
Log: There’s a video of the kid in
the go-kart that keeps
crashing into the wall.
Trog: Yeah, I guess that’s my answer.
Baaulp: That—
Trog: There’s some YouTube
video that’s called like, “Epic
Jared Fail 2003,” or something like that—
Wayne: That is a good fucking answer.
Gir: Is that missing?
Wayne: It was-it was this
video called, “Epic Jared Fail
2003,” where it played a song
from Oneohtrix Point Never
um, where it’s just a
kid in a go-kart like, failing
to move out of this corner and just repeatedly
crashing into the wall over and over again,
surprisingly hard, while his dad
just goes, “Jared! No, Jared you
gotta just go in reverse! Jared!” And he
sounds so fucking like, defeated and sad.
Baaulp: Yeah, it’s like this
dad like, desperately trying to
teach a kid how to like, y’know turn,
like the concept of like, “Alright, back
up and turn the corner,” y’know, and
the kid just does not get it, just slams
into the-slams the go-kart
over and over again [laughs].
Trog: I am—So we’re officially here on Where Do We
Begin, we’re putting out an all-points bulletin—
Wayne: For “Epic Jared Fail 2003.”
Trog: We know we’ve asked for
many things-we’ve asked for
many things in the past, I know we-we
asked for the um, will.i.am entertainment
tonight and you guys managed to find
that, so this is an all-points bulletin
for a video called, “Epic Jared
Fail,” and then some year after it,
either like
2003 or 2005—
Wayne: 2003 or 2005.
Trog: Some year.
Baaulp: And I remember this-I
hope I’m not wrong, ‘cause I
don’t want to lead people astray, but
I remember the go-kart being green.
Log: Why would that matter.
Baaulp: ‘Cause that helps
people-that helps people narrow it
down. It’s a kid in a green go-kart.
Trog: You will definitely know
the video if you manage to
find it, it’s possible that it’s not
even out there, but if it is out there,
please let us know.
Wayne: I can probably find
the OPN song that was in the
video, too. The uh, I don’t
rem—I remember exactly what
it sounds like I just
don’t remember the—
Trog: But yes, we miss that video forever,
it’s very sad
that it’s gone.
Log: Well, there’s that. The
only other thing I can think of
is something that I actually
was able to find recently.
Baaulp: Nice.
Gir: See, I have the same thing as well.
Log: It was like-it was like a
mix that I just couldn’t find
for like eight years, ‘cause it was
something that I only knew of from-it was a
site called JetSetRaid.io, like y’know,
Jet Set Radio but .io, and or, that
might be what exists now, there’s some
site that’s like a radio station site
with a Jet Set Radio theme that plays
songs, whatever. There used to be another
one that was just a list of tracks
and it was like, “Alright, here’s my
recommendations.” Um, there was one on
there that was just a mix with an unknown
artist and it was-I thought it was good, and
it was like-the name of it was in gib-was
like gibberish, too. And that site just
went down at some point and it never
came back up.
Wayne: Before we move too far
on, I did figure out the name
of the song from the Epic Jared Fail
video, it’s the Oneohtrix Point Never –
Replica, that is the song that
plays in the Epic Jared Fail video.
Trog: Please find this for
us. We’ve looked everywhere,
so it’s probably gone, but if it’s not…
Gir: I did have a video, or
rather a person who made videos
that I also could not find for fucking
years at a time, and then a couple
months ago finally discovered it. I
could not tell you the person’s name off
the top of my head right now, but it
was this guy that would make microwave
art, where he would throw shit into a
microwave and then once it came back out
all melted and fucked up and burnt, he
would like stick like eyeballs on-like
plastic eyes onto it and different
colors and shit all over it,
and I remember just
being fascinated by this guy when I was younger.
And then for, I guess in 2010
he got banned from YouTube—
Trog: Damn.
Gir: And that’s why I couldn’t
find him. And then come year 2020
I finally found all his videos,
they were just up on Dailymotion.
Log: That’s cool Gir, but I
wasn’t finished with my story.
Gir: Okay, well my story was better, so.
Log: Mmm.
Gir: Mmm [laughs].
Log: Well, anyways, that site
was gone-that site was gone,
it took me till this year to think, “Oh,
maybe I should just go on the Wayback Machine
on that site, and so I did and it worked,
I mean obviously the songs-the sound
files weren’t there anymore,
but the title was there,
tried Google searching it
but it was just like, like I said,
it was gibberish. I got a Reddit thread by
the guy who made the mix and he was like,
“Hey, I made this mix, go check it
out.” But the link was to fuckin’ Megaupload.
Trog and Gir: Oh no.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: He wanted to send files across the globe!
Gir: Classic.
Wayne: Oh, man.
Log: I was-I was like, “Nooo!
But wait, where do I share my
files across the globe now?” I go on
SoundCloud, I type it in, and what do you
know, somebody uploaded-somebody uploaded
that mix without permission and now
it’s the only source of it existing
in the entire Internet now.
Trog: Hell yeah. Well, hey, you did it, then.
Gir: Gotta love it.
Wayne: My answer’s a lumpsum
of things. I want to see-I wish
I still had access to the first ever
YouTube Poop I ever watched. I remember it
by name, but it doesn’t exist anymore.
I don’t remember who uploaded it, it was
called, uh, it was called, “Youtube
Poop: Insert Your Blank Here,” and it was
like, it was a YouTube Poop of
Egoraptor’s—what were his-what
were his original
series that got him—
Gir: Awesome Series.
Wayne: Yeah, it was like Katamari
Awesome, it was just like
this loop of like the-the King of All
Cosmos saying, “Good work, son, now it’s
time to play on Uranus!” Over and over,
and then like it just would be different
every time. It was the most simple
shit, but I thought it was fuckin’
hilarious. And the other lost videos
that I can’t watch anymore that are
literally gone is every video that was
on my original YouTube account that got
taken down for like a trap video or
whatever. If you don’t know what a trap
video is, it’s whenever you fuckin’ like,
upload a video that’s like, “Halo 3 All
Cheat Codes,” and it’s just a bunch of
loud noises with a thumbnail in the middle
that was popular back in like 2010. That
was like, before they had figured out
the YouTube algorithm, that kind of shit
doesn’t happen anymore. You never get
recommended some shit on YouTube that’s
like, “Wow! Craziest Sharpest Knife in
the World!” And it’s just a bunch
of loud noise, that doesn’t happen.
Trog: Yeah, it’s true.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: They-they definitely
figured out how to stop that
phenomenon, which is funny. Yeah, I
would-I would like to see all my old,
original YouTube Poops. Do you
remember what your earliest
YouTube Poops were called?
Whoever used to make them?
Baaulp: I still have them up.
Gir: Yeah, let me go to my
YouTube Channel and look at them.
Wayne: That’s true,
that’s-you guys actually have them
archived.
Trog: Yeah, I don’t. Mine are gone, unfortunately.
Wayne: My first ever YouTube
Poop was called, “Yoshi likes
to burp,” and it was-it was like Yoshi
burping and Windows Movie Maker stock
sound effects.
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: Let me look, just ‘cause I’m
curious now. Here it is, “YouTube
Poop - Sorry.”
[Wayne, Baaulp, and Trog laugh]
Trog: This question is from
Fae, who asks, “What’s something
that you didn’t like at first but grew on you,
or you revisited and found
things to like about it?”
Wayne: Dead by Daylight.
Gir: Oh yeah, that’s easy for
Wayne. For me, it was Mass
Effect. When I first played
Mass Effect, I fucking hated it.
Wayne: Which one did you start with? One?
Gir: Number one!
Wayne: Yeah.
Gir: I fucking got it-I got
it and I fucking played like
half an hour, I think I didn’t even make
it off—I think I made it off of the like,
main pl-the first planet you’re on, basically
the tutorial planet, and I was like,
“This game fucking sucks! This game
blows, what the fucking big deal about
this?” And then it was-I want to say it
was the summer that Mass Effect 3 came
out or like the summer after, and uh, I was
just really bored and I was like, “Y’know
what? I’m gonna ahead and give this
another try, I didn’t-I don’t even remember
how much of it I played.” And I finished
it all in like a day or two and I was
like, “Well that was fucking fantastic,
let’s move onto the next one." And then
I played all of fuckin two in a couple
days, and then I moved onto three and
uh, saw why everyone was disappointed.
Baaulp: Damn. What a letdown.
You played through the whole
series and then you got to three?
Gir: [Laughs] Yeah. I still like Mass Effect,
there’s still
a lot to like there.
Baaulp: For me it uh, I think
it was Neverwinter Nights.
Gir: Really.
Baaulp: I got a copy from my
cousin when I was a little kid
and I like, didn’t get it as a kid, and
then I revisited it back like, in high
school, I was like, “Woah, this shit is
dope,” and then I was hooked. That is
still a game-I’ve boughten that game
multiple times, and as long as people keep
remastering it, I buy the new version
and then like, I’ll just like—Maybe every
once in a blue moon I go like, “Mmm,
gonna turn that game on, start a new
character, play a little bit of it.” And
then like, every year or so-every two
years or so, I get the hankering to
like beat it from start to finish again.
Trog: For me, this is like,
I-I guess this kind of counts,
whenever I played through Sekiro the
first time, I fucking hated it. Until I
beat the final boss, and immediately
started a second playthrough.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: That game made me so fucking mad.
Gir, laughing: Why did you do that?
Trog: I don’t know.
Gir, laughing: You don’t know!
Wayne: I remember when that
game launched and you like-like,
recounting your tales and experience
with it and being so fuckin’ mad and
shitting on it and I was just like-I
was over here like, “No, baby, no, no.
This is like perfect game for you.”
Trog: [Crosstalk] I was just
shittin’ on it, I was so mad.
Wayne: Trog, you love Souls
games. And then yes, it did—
Trog: I did, I did come around—
Wayne: Sekiro did that to
people, Sekiro did that to a
number of people in our group.
Trog: I know.
Wayne: You hated it, Rex hated
it, Moupi hated it, like, we
had a bunch of friends that just
like, fuckin’ couldn’t stand Sekiro.
Trog: It truly is a bizarre
thing where it-yeah, it just
like, it tricks you into hating it until you beat
it and it’s like wait, I
think I had fun this time.
Wayne: “Fuck this game! I’m gonna play it again.”
Trog: Exactly.
[Gir and Wayne laugh]
Trog: Hey, egg on my face, what can you say.
Wayne: Yeah, like I said, Dead
by Daylight is my answer. Um,
a couple years back I was in a relationship
and uh, my partner had asked me to play
Dead by Daylight with her and like, I’m
of the interest in doing that, like if
my partner asked me to do something
with them I’m going to say yes, ‘cause I
want to bond, so we tried Dead by Daylight
together and I played as a survivor,
and I thought it was just the most boring,
dogshit game. Like I was just like, “Okay,
we-we walk around—” And this was after
Friday the 13th had launched, which is a
very similar game that I very much
enjoyed, I only played the survivor
experience, and I just like ran around
and she was telling me what to do and it’s
like, “Wait, we just run around and go
to these generators and hold down mouse
one and press space every few minutes?”
And like, that was all she could tell
me it was, and I was like, “I can’t
believe this game is that boring." And then
the fact that you couldn’t play killer
with your friends like you could in Friday
the 13th, had me just thinking that that
game was fucking dogshit. And then Scorpy
got into it, he tried for one of his
horror streams a few months back, and uh,
and I was like-for one of his streams
I was like, “Y’know what, I’ll try that
game again,” and me, Gir, and Scorpy
played it, and like, something about it
was just like, there’s something here.
Something about like, the first game I
played coming back was the survivor
mode, and like, something about the fact
that like, the fact that that game is
mostly balanced around the fact that one
team can see in third person and has
this giant FOV and the other team is
powerful but can only see in first person
like, something about like, just hiding
behind a small little box as Scorpy
walked right past me and he didn’t see me,
I was like, “Okay, that’s kind of
neat.” Like, I’m into this concept.
Baaulp: It’s advanced hide and seek.
Wayne: Yeah, when—Advanced
hide and seek, advanced cat and
mouse. And then I-and then I started
playing killer and was like, “Okay,
this is fucking fun.” And now I’m
like, one of my main games, now. Yeah,
that was like a total shift. ‘Cause I like-I
went years like, not only disliking the game,
but expressing to other people how much I
fucking hated it. Like-like a few months back,
Lauren got into it and any time she brought
it up I was like, “How can you play this?
How are you enjoying this?” And she got so
annoyed with me because I couldn’t stop—Like,
something about Dead by Daylight made me so
mad and now I’m a changed man, and I regret—
Trog: [Laughs] Upset you.
Wayne, laughing: Yes.
Gir: Stop having fun!
Log: Uhh… Mustard.
Trog: [Laughs] Yeah, Alright.
Baaulp: The food? Alright?
Wayne: Y’know, actually I change my answer.
I change my
answer. Sex.
[Log laughs]
Trog: Okay.
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: Ya hated it, now ya love it.
Log: Uh, pickles.
Trog: Y’know, I kind of
feel the same about mustard.
Baaulp: That sounds like you just growing up.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: I almost think foods that
you disliked when you were young
and now that you do like is a different question.
Trog: ‘Cause that’s like
literally your physiology of your
body is changing, which causes you to
like or dislike different tastes. But I
agree about mustard. I hated mustard as
a kid, but now I’m all about it. It’s
yummy.
Gir: Mustards good, yeah.
Trog: Mustard is too strong
tasting for a young child, but
delicious for me, an adult.
Wayne: Unless you’re like a fucked up child and
you drink
it.
Gir: Are you talking about me, what?
Log: I hated Street Fighter V, and I still do.
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: That’s not—That doesn’t answer the question.
Gir: That’s not the question.
Wayne: Dude, I was a reverse
situation where I thought I
liked Street Fighter V for a while
and then I hated it. Still hate it.
Baaulp: Damn.
Log: What have I shifted my
opinion on? Usually I feel like I
get it right the first time [unintelligible]—
Baaulp: Damn, Log has never changed his opinion on
anything, he’s been right the first time always.
Wayne: I can’t really explain why in short
words, but that makes perfect sense for Log.
Baaulp: Yeah. I mean I’m
like that about a lot of things,
too. I-I sus out what I like and don’t like ASAP.
Log: Yeah, it’s hard for me—What
was something that I didn’t
like? And I came back to it?
Baaulp: Maybe you don’t have
anything, you don’t have
anything—You don’t have to have an answer.
Log: ‘Cause I feel like it
makes no sense that I wouldn’t
have something like that ‘cause
there’s so much stuff out there.
But what could
it be?
Trog: I just usually don’t commit that kind of
stuff to
memory.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: I just know Sekiro
‘cause it happened recently.
Baaulp: Yeah, that’s the thing.
Gir: I remember Mass Effect
because it was such a big flip.
Trog: Whenever I was a kid, I
didn’t like rap. But-but then
I listened to wrap and I
thought, “Yeah, this is good.”
Log: Yeah. Yeah I feel like that’s—
Wayne: Music is definitely a
strong contender for your
choice for this question.
Gir: I’ll admit I was the
kid in like, sixth grade that
said, “I like all music except rap or country.”
Trog: A classic.
Log: I feel like whenever I
was a kid I just had like, a
general disdain for music. Like,
I don’t care about any songs.
Trog: That’s wild to say.
Gir: That’s how I am now.
[Wayne laughs]
Log: I mean I only heard songs that
played on like, the car
radio and that was it.
Trog: Sure, yeah.
Wayne: You played video games. Video
game music, like video
game music?
Log: Yeah, I guess—I mean like,
there’d be like one song per
game that I would put on a loop and that’d be it.
Wayne: I was that kind of kid,
where like, when I was young
I didn’t pay attention, I didn’t have
favorite bands except for like, just
stuff my dad listened to that I also liked—
Gir: Oh my god. I—
Wayne: —like I thought Styx was
one of my favorite bands and
it’s absolutely not, however, I still
do like that one song by Styx, it’s
called like, Renegade, I think?
That’s the only one I remember.
Trog: That’s a good one.
Wayne: [Singing] I’m a
wanted man. But, the uh—I was
the kind of kid that fuckin’ loved video game
music, so like when I was in third grade I got
one of the earliest iPods and I would go to
VGMusic.net so I’d just have like, Star Wolf
theme on my—Star Wolf theme MIDI on my iPod and
it was like, that is what I would listen to.
Gir: I know Log is struggling
to think of his answer, but I
just thought of an alternate answer
for something that I didn’t like, like
something I hated, but now
I-I do enjoy. Uh, Scorpy.
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: [Laughs] Yeah!
Baaulp: Oh man.
Wayne: Y’know what, me too! Me fuckin’ too.
[Gir laughs]
Wayne: Scorpy pissed me off.
Scorpy was this fuckin’—he was
like the YouTube Poop Steam
Chat equivalent of an upstart—
Gir: He was an asshole.
Wayne: —where he just showed
up, was an asshole, and he just
got Admin on the TF2 server
inexplicably for no reason—
Trog: It made no sense.
Wayne: —and he was just a fuckin’ dick!
Gir: He was an asshole [laughs]. He was a dick!
Trog: People can change.
Wayne: Now he’s like one of the nicest
people I know
[laughs].
Gir: Yeah, now he’s a great friend.
Trog: Yeah, but it is funny.
Baaulp: Scorpy’s dope.
Trog: Yeah, no, I remember
being indignant about that as
well. I was like, “Who the fuck is this
Scorpy guy, he literally just walks in
and gets Admin? What the fuck?” Like,
I still don’t know how that happened.
Wayne: He got Mod in the Steam Chat
and he got Admin on the TF2 server,
and like specifically Admin on the TF2 server,
I resented him so much for that because, like—
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: Mhmm.
Wayne: —Mod in the Steam
Chat, that’s one thing. That’s
whatever. But Admin on the
TF2 server, that was a fucking
coveted seat, because
you could do shit—
Gir: That was a golden ticket.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: —You were playing a different game if you
were an Admin on the YouTube Poop TF2 server.
Trog: [Laughs] You could just fuck around.
Wayne: Yeah.
Baalp: Yeah, we were-we were
playing TF2 like every day.
Wayne: Scorpy would just like,
spend his time putting on
like, derogatory like, mocking hats on
people forcibly and spawning pumpkins on
them and blowing them up while
they’re trying to play TF2.
Trog: Yeah.
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: See, I didn’t help that
by making a hat replacement
that was just a big dick.
[Trog and Wayne laugh]
Wayne: [Inhales loudly] I’m just
thinking of that one guy-that
one guy who played Scout that was so
laggy that he moved slower than every
other class, and you would
put the hats on him and—
[Gir, Baaulp, Trog, and Wayne laugh]
Trog: Oh man, good times on the
TF2 server. The battledrobe.
Wayne: Yeah, very different times.
Gir: The battledrobe.
Trog: What a classic.
Log: I have nothing.
Gir: Log got nothing, Log has
liked everything he’s liked
and hated everything he hated.
Log: I like everything on the
first try. That’s kind of how
it goes for me, is like I-like I—I feel
like I generally have a good opinion of
stuff going in until it does-until it-it—
Gir: Until it sours it?
Log: Until it-until it bites
the hand that feeds it, and
then I throw it in the dumpster
and I never speak of it again.
Wayne: Sawsily asks, “What’s the best YouTube
comment you’ve
ever seen?”
Trog: Oh my god, that’s
impossible. I’ve seen so many!
Wayne: There’s so many good
ones. We got a whole blog
dedicated to it.
Trog: We have a Tumblr dedicated to it, yeah.
Wayne: Okay, okay maybe that
one is too like, divisive.
Trog: I’d say, for that question,
just a generic answer is: go
look at the comment-tube Tumblr,
and that’s our collective answer.
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: Iprix on our Discord
server asks, “What contests or
competitions have the crew been in?
How did they go? Does going hotdog
eating
contest?”
[Trog and Baaulp laugh]
Gir: Yeah, going hotdog eating contest.
Wayne: Not quite sure what you’re asking there at
the end,
uh—
Trog: Don’t take this the wrong way,
this is not an invitation to spam the
question’s channel with nonsense, I only
brought this one up because I think this
person made a genuine mistake,
which makes it actually funny.
Wayne: [Laughs] Yeah, like—
Trog: It’s not funny if you
just say nonsense and you know
you’re saying it. It’s only funny if
you fucked up and said something wrong.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: I was in a lot of
competitions as a kid, mostly
because of my being in band, y’know
like, you do-you do—there’s like a lot of
competition in band and stuff in high
school, and even in middle school. I’m
trying to think if there’s anything
that I entered by myself, though.
Baaulp: Yeah, every competition
thing I was entered into was
like, forcibly, like, “Oh, science fair?
I don’t want to do science fair, science
is fuckin’ lame. Well, we’re going to
do science fair,” and because I was also
trying to get a good grade I was usually
picked I was like, “Well, what—I-I
don’t-I don’t want this.” I remember in
high school, doing an experiment that I
thought would get me a good grade, but
was mediocre enough for me to like, not
have to do the school science fair,
where like I competed against like other
classes, and I still had to-I was still
the best in my class, I was like, “This
is bullshit, fuck this.”
Wayne: I feel like any contest
I entered when I was a kid, I
like, repressed because I lost, and it
was bad. Like, I don’t think I ever won
any big contest or anything like that.
I know a story like, Scorpy told back in
the YouTube Poop Steam Chat days, where
like he-when he moved to Canada as an
English speaking kid he got put in a
English spelling bee with a bunch of
French kids and just dominated them.
[Trog and Baaulp laugh]
Gir: That’s fucking funny.
Trog: That’s good.
Gir: I don’t remember it—There’s two things, I
was told about this because I don’t remember,
it was when I was really little, but
I was in like a, egg and spoon race—
Trog: Hell yeah.
Wayne: Woo.
Gir: And I was told that I was
like, second or third place,
however, the entire time I had my
hand on the egg, I was just cheating.
Trog: Nice.
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: Oh, so that’s like a
good outcome, where you just
cheated and you got second so
that’s like, take what you can get.
Gir: I think I got good luck in terms of that
kind of shit
[laughs].
Log: You still lost?
Gir: No, I won, like second
or third or whatever. Um, they
didn’t-I don’t think they noticed I was cheating.
Trog: Well, second or third isn’t winning,
just thought I should point that out.
Log: [Laughs] Yeah.
Gir: It’s not last place,
bitch, therefore it’s winning.
Log: But the-your hand was on the egg?
Gir: Uh-huh. And then the
second thing was, like Baaulp
said, a science fair contest thing. Where
I didn’t want to do it, ‘cause like you said,
we were forced to,
so I was like, “Fuck it,
I’m just gonna do like a potato battery, or
something,” and this was like, middle school.
So, I-I got a potato, got like
a-the thing that tests current,
stuck it in the potato, was like, “I think
there’s a current? Fuck this,” and then
I downloaded somebody else’s project, and
presented it, and got second place [laughs].
Trog: Ah, yes.
Baaulp: No, you had to run the
gambit, that’s-that’s the problem,
you gotta be mediocre. You should
have stuck with the potato.
Gir: I got second place for—No,
it was another-I downloaded
somebody else’s potato report! I plagiarized it.
Baaulp: Oh.
Wayne: I plagiarized when I—I
think I told this story on one
of the podcasts, where I plagiarized my
sister’s traced Spiderman drawing for
an art contest at one point.
[Gir laughs]
Trog, laughing: Oh no.
Wayne: Which is like, double
bad because like, one, it was
clearly on tracing paper and was
traced, and two, I didn’t do it.
Trog: Yeah. Yeah.
[Gir laughs]
Wayne: I actually did think of
an answer of a time I was in like
a, sort of competition where like, I
used to go to like, summer camp, not like
stay-away, it was just kind of this thing
where like you would, like during the
day on certain days of the week during
summer you’d like go up to the school
and you would just do like fun shit.
It was like-it was like parks and rec
camp. I think that’s what it was called.
Baaulp: Yeah, I know that.
Wayne: We were playing like, Camp
Jeopardy, and like, and there
were like teams—it was like team Camp
Jeopardy, and I think the winner of the
team got like, coupons to get free sodas
at lunch or something like that, and
this actually ties into what I was talking
about earlier, how I used to listen
to video game music when I was a kid. And
the final question in one of the categories,
I don’t remember what the category was
about, I think it was music, and it was
like the one for the highest points,
and it was like, if you got that one you
won, and the question was—I remember,
I specifically remember the guy pulling
out the card and he was like, “What is
the name of the song that plays on the
title screen of the hit game,
Kingdom Hearts?” And I instantly
like [claps once]
hand shot up—
Baaulp: Ohhh.
Wayne: “Dearly Beloved.”
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: That is the nerdiest
fucking fact to know when you’re
in like, fourth grade, but knowing that
fact, everyone went fucking apeshit
over that, and I was like, the
hero, and I got everyone soda.
Baaulp: Nice, nice. When you’re a kid like, a lot
of people are like, “Oh, kids need competition,”
and you’re right, but they should get to pick,
you can’t like, you don’t-you can’t force kids
into competition ‘cause they’ll hate it. This
uh, I remember one year-I remember one year,
when I was in middle school I remember getting
our schedule and going like, “Wait a minute,
I don’t have gym!” And apparently what they
did was they just took half like-they just
took half the kids in my grade, like fourth
grade-or not fourth grade, in whatever,
right? Whatever grade, and instead of gym we
had dance class, which none of us signed up for,
and so like half the grade was like, “What the
fuck? We got dance class?” And then there’s
like a dance competition and it was like, “We
didn’t want this! What?” [Laughs] You can’t—
Gir: That sounds like shit.
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: It was so shitty.
Gir: Oh, no! Baaulp, you just
unlocked a fucking hidden
memory in my brain, I fucking had
to learn square dancing in like,
fourth
grade.
Baaulp: Oh my god.
Wayne: Yeah, I mean we’ve
talked about that on our streams
before like, I had to learn square dancing, too.
Gir: Fuck that! Square dancing sucks!
Trog: I never did. And I live in Texas.
Wayne: All I remember is-all
I remember is the do-si-do.
Baaulp: I don’t know why! We-none of us knew
why. None of us knew why. I don’t even think the
dance teachers knew why they were there because
like, I wanted gym like everyone else! And the
worst part was like, kids would be like, “Haa,
you got dance class.” And it was like, “Yeah,
half of us have dance class you asshole [laughs].
Like, we didn’t pick this, no one picked this!”
Trog: Baaulp talking about
splitting a bunch of kids up into
two arbitrary groups unlocked a
memory in my brain of a elementary
school field day, y’know like, you guys
had a field day at some point, right?
Just like a bunch of little games or whatever.
Gir: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wayne: And they were a blast.
Trog: I’m realizing now how
fucked up it was, and also the
fact that this memory has stayed in
my head this long shows that it’s
fucked up, is that we did a field day
on elemen-like in elementary school, and
they’re just supposed to be a bunch
of fun games that you play, right?
Baaulp: Uh-huh.
Trog: But at the end they gave
everybody either first place
or second place.
Baaulp: What?
Trog: Yeah! Like they—
Gir: Oh, it was one of those deals. No losers.
Trog: But as a third grader
it’s like, “What the fuck?” Or
even as an adult, I’m thinking about
it’s like, what did they judge these kids
on? Why did they just arbitrarily decide
some kids get first place and some
kids get second place, and I
got second place and I was so
fucking mad. I’m
still mad.
[Wayne and Baaulp laugh]
Trog: Why did I get second
place? Why-why was I bad at the
fucking egg toss, like, what the fuck?
[Wayne laughs]
Log: You didn’t cheat. You shoulda kept your
hand on the
egg.
Gir: Yeah.
Baaulp: Trog, they were judging
you on how much fun you were
having, you weren’t having enough fun.
Trog: I wasn’t having enough fun.
Wayne: You weren’t positive enough.
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: I just think it’s fucked
up to take a bunch of eight-year
olds and then like, have them all play
a bunch of games and then decide at the
end who’s the winners and who’s the losers.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Gir: Yeah, that’s like worst than first,
second, third, and
then like, participant.
Trog: Yeah, because it’s literally
just first or second place,
you either won or you lost.
Gir: You were either good or you weren’t good.
Trog: Yeah. Fucked up.
Gir: That’s worse for morale.
Baaulp: Yeah, that’s kind of shitty.
Trog: Oh, and then the other
competition that I just
remember was that one time I was a kid and
I went to the Texas State Fair they-I-I
did a game where I ran around a bunch
of barrels and pretended to be a horse.
[Wayne, Baaulp, and Gir laugh]
Baaulp: What-what was your horse name?
Trog: I didn’t have a horse name.
[Baaulp and Wayne laugh]
Gir: Chuckles.
Log: I don’t think I ever won
a competition that mattered. I
know I won the spelling bee at my school
whenever I was in sixth grade, and
that meant that I went on to like the
county spelling bee or something, or like
a district, I don’t know.
Trog: Mhmm.
Log: And it’s like-it’s one of
those things where it’s like
you don’t prepare for it if
you’re part of it ‘cause like,
who gives a shit,
right?
Gir: Mhmm.
Log: It’s a spelling bee. But
even so, whenever I got to
that district spelling bee,
and I lost, I was still mad,
I was like, “What the
fuck was that word?”
Trog, laughing: Yeah.
[Baaulp laughs]
Log: It’s like, why are you
giving me this hard word and
everybody else is getting easy words.
Baaulp: You’re still mad even though you were
like-you didn’t
care?
Log: I think that’s why I tend
to avoid competitions like,
if I’m in a competition, I want to fuckin’ win.
Trog: Yeah.
Log: And if I don’t win I get pissed.
[Gir and Trog laugh]
Gir: Yeah, that’s how I feel, too.
Baaulp: I’m a pretty competitive
person, but I have to like,
enjoy it. I-I was very uncompetitive in
school but only because I was already being
forced into so many competitive things
that I was like, “Fuck this.” Like, now I
like competitive video games, right?
But like, back then it’s like, “I don’t
want to do the science fair.” “Well you
gotta do the science fair.” “I don’t want
dance class.” “Well you gotta do dance
class, and we’re also splitting you up
into groups and you have to dance
against each other,” It’s like—
Wayne: Well in dance class-in
dance class you don’t get to
hit the sick combos, so it’s not the same.
Baaulp, laughing: Yeah.
Wayne: Not the same as fighting games.
Gir: You were in a bad dance class, then.
Log: I remember back in our
YouTube Poop Steam group,
there-there was a guy, and I’m not even
gonna like, even name names, but there
was a guy that for whatever reason, just
bought every game, and then on Christmas
he had just like a Christmas art
competition. I don’t know why he had that.
Gir: Oh, yeah! I forgot about that.
Wayne: [Unintelligible] That.
Log: And it was like, “Alright,
alright, draw pictures and
if you win we’ll give you games.” And
I guess for whatever reason I was the
only person in the entire group that
like, actually decided tthat, “Oh, if I
try, I’ll win a game,” and I did, and
I drew a picture that I actually like,
put some effort into, and naturally
I’m the only person in the entire group
that put any effort in and so
I won the first prize [laughs].
Trog: Hey, you did it. Yeah,
none of us were, y’know—
Log: But that like, barely counts—like you
guys-like you guys were all going in there
just like, you guys were all going in there
trying to lose. So that barely even counts.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: I mean it makes sense
for that group of people, for
that group of children, essentially.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: That none of us would try.
Wayne: Hey, so I did find-I
did find our podcast thumbnail
picture in the Discord right there, but
the picture also unlocked a memory of
mine. Does Balloon Blast count as a contest?
Trog: It can.
Log: I don’t think so, I
think it’s too small scale.
Baaulp: I think it’s a scam.
Wayne: I think if there’s four
players it’s a contest, you’re
competing with other children.
Baaulp: Okay. What about it?
Wayne: So I was playing Balloon
Blast or an equivalent at a
carnival, and I’ve told you guys this
story before, but we were playing the
game, and I won, and the-the reason
that I was playing that game was because
they had cool Sonic plushies, and that
was fuckin’ rare that you would see that
at a carnival, and you win, and the fuckin’
carnie comes over and he holds Sonic
and Knuckles up to you and he says, “Do
you want red Sonic or blue Sonic?” And
I got so fuckin’ mad.
[Gir laughs]
Wayne: That’s bullshit, man.
Gir: “I want blue Knuckles!”
Wayne: “Do you want red
Knuckles or blue Knuckles?”
That’s even
funnier.
[Baaulp and Gir laugh]
Wayne: [Laughs] You don’t know
Sonic, but you do know Knuckles.
Log: Against my better judgement,
I still enter competitions.
I’m in one right now, uh, if I win, you
won’t hear the end of it, and if I lose,
you won’t hear about it ever again.
[Everyone laughs]
Gir: Aw man, y’know, reflecting on
all this has made me
realize something.
Trog: Mhmm.
Gir: When I was a kid,
I constantly lied and cheated and
stole.
Wayne: I loved Balloon Blast.
Baaulp: Yeah, you were a bad kid!
Gir: I was a shit kid [laughs]!
Wayne: You were a bad boy.
Gir: But the best part is… I
always got away with it [laughs].
Baaulp: Damn.
Trog: Well, you weren’t ever punished. Now
that’s why you
stole a lot.
Gir: Nobody ever caught me!
Wayne: Okay, I’m not gonna go-I’m not
gonna go into details, but I-for me,
it’s the same way, until I did
get caught. And then it was bad,
but I won’t go into details
because I can’t go into details.
Trog: [Laughs] It built up
and-and you-you got all your
negative karma out on the same instant.
Wayne: Yeah, and then my life’s
been great since then! After
I met those horrible consequences.
Gir: I-I stopped when, oh, you
know what? No, there was one
time where I got caught, and there
were some pretty bad consequences.
Wayne: [Laughs] See? You always-you
do always get caught! It
might not happen until like,
sixteen years into your life, but you will get
caught.
Gir: Here’s the thing though,
is I got caught, but that
thing that I got caught doing, I ended up doing-I
still do it to this day, uh, ‘cause
it’s piracy.
Wayne: Oh, did you get a notice from your ISP?
Gir: Because we lived in Germany,
and we got a notice, and
it was a 900 Euro fine.
Trog: Damn.
Baaulp and Wayne: Oooooh.
Wayne: That sucks.
Gir: Yeah, uh,
I did not like Eidos or Batman: Arkham Asylum
for a long time because of that.
[Trog and Wayne laugh]
Trog: Specifically—it’s not their fault you
stole their
game!
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: I know! But because I
downloaded Batman: Arkham Asylum
from Pirate Bay, uh I got in big, big trouble.
Baaulp: We gotta wrap up
soon, but I-I-I want to add my
thing onto that. I think some—Looking
back at my childhood, especially like in
school, grade school taught me how to
like, social engineer people. Like, I was
not a troublemaker, but I loved just
like, wandering around and like, in school
you’re not supposed to do that, but like,
I would-I like-at some point like, in
grade school I just learned to play
it cool, and just be like, “Oh no, I’m
supposed to be here, this
teacher told me to be here.”
Gir, laughing: Yeah!
Baaulp: Like I would just like,
I would just like take the
info I knew and like, corrobor—like,
build these stories and like, it worked.
Gir: Nah, I did that shit, too.
Baaulp: I remember asking to
go to the bathroom for a class
and then just like, wandering around, and—
[Trog laughs]
Gir: Yeah, I did that in high school all the time!
Baaulp: Yeah! And like a teacher
would stop me and be like—like
I would go into classrooms and be like,
“Oh, yeah, y’know, can I just
hang out in here [laughs]?”
Gir: Oh, you were one of the
kids that would just go into a
random class?
Trog: That’s so crazy. I
couldn’t fathom ever doing that.
Gir: That’s funny.
Baaulp: This is not something I
utilize as an adult and definitely
not for nefarious purposes, but
as a kid I did that all the time.
Gir: Definitely.
Baaulp: Dude, I got free
McDonald’s one time ‘cause I
met this kid, I think I’ve told this
story, I met this kid at a park and was
like, “Yo, what if—” And like, these
were like, these were like definitely
white, suburban parents who were like,
“Ooh, it would be so cool if our son
knew a first generation immigrant son,”
and I knew that, so I was like, “Oooh,”
and I hung out with this kid, I
got free McDonald’s. I never-I—
Wayne: Baaulp, Baaulp, Baaulp.
That makes perfect sense.
Trog: Yeah.
Gir: Yeah.
[Baaulp and Wayne laugh]
Gir: I did the same kind of
shit though in high school where
I would just be like, “Hey, I need to
go to the bathroom, sign this bathroom
pass for me?” It’s like, “Sure, okay.”
I would leave the classroom and then I
would just go for a walk.
Wayne: There were definitely
a few kids in my life who I
would hang out with just ‘cause
they had good snacks at their house.
Gir: That’s funny.
Wayne: Like this one kid? He
always had Dunkaroos. You think
my mom would buy Dunkaroos? No. My mom
and dad would never buy that fucking
sugar trash. But this kid always had them.
Gir: That’s like the
dork neighbor I had where
I did not really like him,
but I was friends with him
because his dad could put cheats on my
GameBoy, and because he-he and I would
go to the pool, I would just
go to the pool for free.
Baaulp: There was a-there was
this—Oh my god. You guys aren’t
gonna even believe me because this is like,
such a weird thing. When I was a freshman
in high school, there was a kid that I
swear to god was the same age as us, but
this kid had a f—this kid was like
Russian, they had a full beard, and they
always had fruit snacks. And it was
dope, because he would always hand out
fruit snacks. But he had a full beard,
and we were all like, “How do you have a
full beard?” And he was like, “I don’t know.”
Trog: [Laughs] He was scared of it.
Gir: [Laughs] I don’t know,
this is scary. It won’t go away.
Wayne: Wait, wait. Hold on,
I’m sorry. I zoned out, did you
say that was like, a Halloween thing?
Baaulp: No.
[Gir laughs]
Baaulp: This—
Wayne: Who gave you—A bearded
man gave you Fruit by the Foot
on Halloween, right?
Baaulp: Yeah. Let’s-yeah, sure.
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: Do you guys have any
scary Halloween stories? Not
like-not like Jason, Friday the 13th—
Baaulp: No.
Trog: We have to end the podcast.
Baaulp and Trog: We have to end it.
Baaulp: We have to end it!
Trog: It’s two hours.
Wayne: No, ‘cause you-‘cause
you—‘Cause me mishearing what you
just said reminded me of a time on
Halloween where we went to this one guy’s
house and the door was just open,
and he was sitting in his living room
watching TV and he told us to walk
into the hallway to get the candy—
Gir: I had the same thing happen!
Wayne: And it was like-it was on the dresser
and like, it’s probably not smart of us kids
to do that, and we were definitely all freaked
out, but we did do that, and he definitely—
Trog: ‘Cause the candy was more important.
Wayne: He definitely-‘cause
it was like—He had good candy,
he had like Crunch bars and shit,
but like, it was very suspicious but
we just like—and we all knew it, too,
I think, like when we walked in, ‘cause
we definitely did just walk in, we
grabbed the candy bars, we just peaced the
fuck out of there. It just-it wasn’t a
malicious dude, it was just genuinely a lazy
fuck who couldn’t be asked
to give the kids the candy,
he’d rather have them
walk into his home.
Gir: I had the same thing
happen except it was—it wasn’t
just us, it was us and our parents. Somebody
was just in their living room watching
TV and they’re like, “Yeah, just come
in and get some candy.” It’s like, you
can’t even be on the fuckin’ porch? Alright ma’am.
Whatever. Nice place you got
here, bye. I couldn’t imagine.
Trog, in a sing-song voice:
And that’s the end of our show.
Gir: I was gonna say, you know
what else I couldn’t imagine?
Ending this podcast.
Trog: I couldn’t imagine this
podcast ending any sooner.
Baaulp: I’m so hungry!
Wayne: Chat if you’re listening-if
you’re listening to this
episode on Halloween—
Gir: Yeah, chat.
Wayne: The-I do that all the time, you fuck.
[Gir and Trog laugh]
Wayne: If you listen to this
episode on Halloween, the uh,
we do have bowls of candy out
for our listeners, my-if you, um—
Gir: One.
Wayne: One per listener. Don’t
take any more than that, but
I do have Mr. Goodbars if you want ‘em.
Gir: I like Mr. Goodbar.
Wayne: Well, you don’t get any,
‘cause they’re for our
listeners.
Gir: I listened!
Wayne: That’s true.
Baaulp: Ayeee, what are we-what
are we doing? Plug us. Plug
our shit.
Wayne: We’re not done with the
candy joke. You have to
finish the joke, first.
Trog: I’m done with the candy joke.
[Baaulp and Wayne laugh]
Gir: Baaulp, we’re trying to tell a joke. You-you
fucked it
up.
Wayne: [Laughs] Okay. Hey, thanks for
listenin’ everybody, this is Where Do We Begin,
we didn’t know where we were gonna start this
shit—We started it with smells, it was bad,
but we know we’re gonna wrap it up. We know how
it’s ending. If you want more content from us,
of course you can hit us up on our
Discord, discord.gg/wayneradiotv,
where you can get announcements for podcasts,
my live streams, the crew’s livestreams,
everything all on one. If you want to find
me specifically, just Google WayneRadioTV,
I’m on Twitch, I’m on Twitter, I’m on all
that. And if you want to find my friends…
Gir: Too bad.
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne: Yep, that was a segue
for you to start talking!
Baaulp: Uh, you can look me
up, I’m Baaulp, B-A-A-U-L-P on
YouTube, Twitter, Twitch. Find my
vids, find my streams, watch ‘em!
Wayne: Most websites you can find Baaulp.
Trog: Baaulp’s got an easy one,
he’s the only Baaulp around.
Log: Yeah, Google Gather Ye
Power, you’ll figure it out.
It’s
easy.
Wayne: It’s a good one! He just
came out with a new chapter,
it’s one of his best yet, lots of laughs in that.
Gir: It is.
Wayne: MasterGir, what about you?
Gir: Easy enough to find,
literally MasterGir on virtually
every fucking platform. Twitch,
Twitter, YouTube, fuckin’—
Wayne: Also known—new name,
MasterGear. Trog, how ‘bout you?
Gir: That’s right, Wayner!
Trog: Uh, I am on Twitch.tv as
T-R-0-G, and I am on Twitter
as Trogort, T-R-O-G-O-R-T.
Wayne: Alright, and—
Gir: Like a palindrome-type deal.
Wayne: Wrap of the night, let’s
all-let’s all start shooting
our water guns at the clowns to make balloons pop.
Baaulp: Okay, okay—
Gir: Thank god you said water balloons.
[Everyone makes water gun sounds]
Wayne: Aw, the clown’s moving!
Gir: Mine’s not working!
Baaulp: I’m tired!
[Water gun sounds continue]
Wayne: Ha ha!
Gir: Mine’s not—What the fuck!
Wayne: Aw, what the fuck! My
balloon was bigger than yours
when it popped!
Baaulp: I’m not-I’m not gonna
get blue Sonic at this rate.
Trog: Lost a banana.
Gir, laughing: Blue Sonic!
Wayne: Wait, I thought yours
popped. I thought his popped! I
thought he made the pop sound!
Gir: I thought you made it!
Wayne: No! Whose balloon popped?
Baaulp: Wait. Wait.
Log: I’m-I’m getting—
Wayne: Where’s the carnival? What’s happening?
[Trog laughs]
[Static sound begins]
Wayne: Oh god.
Log: I’m getting X rank.
Baaulp: Oh my god, it’s getting-oh no,
there’s-there’s a
real ghost!